好吧12:31我认为50岁，还有一些冒险，但看起来以为我认为我们是
all right 12:31 I thought 50 and some risking but look thought I think we are
risking but look thought I think we are maybe 10 20 slides residuals from
第3课可能会有10 20张幻灯片残差，因为我要尝试
maybe 10 20 slides residuals from lecture 3 because I'm going to try to
lecture 3 because I'm going to try to cover them sort of part just the
涵盖它们的一部分，只是概念，实际上并没有什么
cover them sort of part just the concepts there's nothing really
concepts there's nothing really substantial there and and hopefully in
在那里，希望在今天的大部分演讲中我都想要
substantial there and and hopefully in the majority of the lecture today I want
the majority of the lecture today I want to go through some examples of
通过参数化条件分布的一些例子
to go through some examples of parametrized conditional distributions
parametrized conditional distributions right we said the this directed graphs
是的，我们说这个有向图是用局部条件定义的
right we said the this directed graphs are defined with local conditional
are defined with local conditional probability so we need to see how we
概率，所以我们需要查看如何参数化主机，然后再给您
probability so we need to see how we parameterize host and then I'll give you
parameterize host and then I'll give you an example a little bit ahead of the
一个比计划提前一点的例子这里是一个关于你如何做的例子
an example a little bit ahead of the schedule here an example of how you
schedule here an example of how you compute the parameters on those
给定一些条件，计算那些条件分布上的参数
compute the parameters on those conditional distributions given some
conditional distributions given some data the other part I don't think we're
数据的另一部分，我认为我们今天将无法实现
data the other part I don't think we're going to be able to reach it today
going to be able to reach it today it's basically an example so I even will
这基本上是一个例子，所以我什至会在下次使用口头等待时介绍它
it's basically an example so I even will cover it on the next use the oral wait
cover it on the next use the oral wait until maybe a month or two down the road
直到大概一两个月
提醒一下，我们已经看到了三个有针对性的独立关系
cover it on the next use the oral wait until maybe a month or two down the road
so reminder we have seen three independent relationships for directed
提醒一下，我们已经看到了三个有针对性的独立关系
independent relationships for directed graphs basically the most powerful was
基本上最强大的图形就是这种基于分离的常数
graphs basically the most powerful was this constant of this separation based
this constant of this separation based on this biggest ball algorithm or at
这个最大的球算法或至少最大的骨骼结构规则
on this biggest ball algorithm or at least the biggest bone structure rules
本质上，Talgo a既可用于有向图也可用于无向图
in essence the Talgo a to operate for both directed and undirected graphs for
both directed and undirected graphs for direct blocks we said we have to pay
我们说过直接块，我们必须注意这些B结构
direct blocks we said we have to pay attention to these B structures the
attention to these B structures the explaining away we have seen this
解释一下，我们已经看到了这个定向的本地马尔可夫财产，并且
explaining away we have seen this directed local Markov property and
directed local Markov property and edenal descendants this is the
伊甸园的后代，这是前辈，没有任何真正的
edenal descendants this is the predecessors and without really any
predecessors and without really any rigorous proof we basically said these
严格的证明我们基本上说这些关系等同于每个
rigorous proof we basically said these relationships are equivalent to each
relationships are equivalent to each other right if you start with one you
其他权利，如果您从一个开始，您就可以解决其余的问题，而所有这些都是
other right if you start with one you can solve the rest and all of them are
can solve the rest and all of them are actually equivalent to a factorization
实际上等同于的联合分布的因式分解
actually equivalent to a factorization of the Joint Distribution in in over the
of the Joint Distribution in in over the graph that takes this point okay so in
可以理解这一点的图形，所以如果您还记得这一点的话
graph that takes this point okay so in in if you remember with this some
in if you remember with this some examples what we started with the
举例说明我们是从这样的因式分解开始的，然后我们
examples what we started with the factorization like this and then we
factorization like this and then we proved this village you remember by
通过边缘化证明了您记得的这个村庄，所有这些
proved this village you remember by doing marginalization and all of these
doing marginalization and all of these things the lefty way the idea now is
当我从这个开始时，事情就变成了现在的想法
things the lefty way the idea now is when I'm going to start with this and
when I'm going to start with this and try to prove this you know if this not
尝试证明这一点，如果您未从图表中确定这一点，则可以知道这一点
try to prove this you know if this not established from the graph then this
established from the graph then this follows and this is what we need okay
跟着，这就是我们需要的好吧
follows and this is what we need okay all right
all right so just if you think that sort of you
因此，即使您认为您必须要选择分配类型或家庭类型
so just if you think that sort of you have to type of distribution or family
have to type of distribution or family of distributions one the family of
的分布之一就是这种分布的分布家族
of distributions one the family of distributions that factorizes this way
distributions that factorizes this way over the graph and then another family
在图上，然后另一个分布族满足所有
over the graph and then another family of distributions to satisfies all the
of distributions to satisfies all the independence relations defined by the
由图定义的独立关系则基本上是定理
independence relations defined by the graph then basically theorem which is
graph then basically theorem which is more or less we highlighted says that
我们强调指出，这两个分布公式是
more or less we highlighted says that this two distribution formulas are the
this two distribution formulas are the same okay so the distributions the
好的，所以分配SUBSCRIBE独立关系
same okay so the distributions the SUBSCRIBE independence relations the
SUBSCRIBE independence relations the conditional independence relations
由图或
conditional independence relations applied by the graph or the
applied by the graph or the distributions of a price of like this
像这样的价格分布，它们基本上是两个分布
distributions of a price of like this they are basically the two distributions
they are basically the two distributions all the same okay again I'm not gonna be
一切都很好，我不会重复我们已经讨论过的事情，所以
all the same okay again I'm not gonna be repeating things we have discussed so
repeating things we have discussed so let me bring some definition I don't
让我提出一些定义，我认为我们不会大量使用，但是它
let me bring some definition I don't think we will make enormous use but it
think we will make enormous use but it is something you may come across in the
是您可能在文献中遇到过的东西，因此对什么是
is something you may come across in the literature so this definition of what is
literature so this definition of what is called the re equivalent I standing from
叫我从独立中脱颖而出的等价物，所以对于给定图，Z的I
called the re equivalent I standing from independence so I of Z for a given graph
independence so I of Z for a given graph G is the set of all the conditional
G是所有条件独立性陈述的集合，并由
G is the set of all the conditional independence statements and called it by
independence statements and called it by the graph what's the definition so for
该图的定义是什么，例如，在前一种情况下，
the graph what's the definition so for example in the previous case let's say
example in the previous case let's say if this were all the relations for this
如果这是该图的所有关系，那么您知道我的GR的关系
if this were all the relations for this graph then you know I of G R of this
graph then you know I of G R of this relation okay so it's to set or for
关系好，所以可以在本语句中设置或进行条件化
relation okay so it's to set or for conditioning in the present statement
conditioning in the present statement and coded by the graph and two blocks we
并由图和两个块编码，如果G 1的I为
and coded by the graph and two blocks we call them I equivalent if I of G 1 is
call them I equivalent if I of G 1 is equal to I of G 2 and you can show if G
等于G 2的I，您可以显示G 1和G 2是否具有相同的无向
equal to I of G 2 and you can show if G 1 and G 2 have the same undirected
1 and G 2 have the same undirected skeleton and the same set of be
骨架和相同的一组be结构我等效，所以
skeleton and the same set of be structures there I equivalent okay so
structures there I equivalent okay so they have the same independence
他们有我将要处理的相同的独立关系
they have the same independence relations I am only going to process
relations I am only going to process these things that I marked here with red
这些我在这里用红酒标记的东西
these things that I marked here with red wine and
对于定向玻璃非常重要，它说我们只能识别图形
very important for directed glass it says we can only identify graph
says we can only identify graph structures are equivalent so basically
结构是等价的，所以基本上，如果您尝试识别，我会说
structures are equivalent so basically if you try to identify I would say the
if you try to identify I would say the directions are closed is it to the left
方向是关闭的，无论是向左还是向右，您都无法执行
directions are closed is it to the left or to the right you do not be able to do
or to the right you do not be able to do that okay
可以，而且在很多方面都没有限制
that okay and in many ways not to limitation
and in many ways not to limitation basically of the directed glass but then
基本上是有向玻璃的，但是直接有图的性质
basically of the directed glass but then there are properties of directly graphs
there are properties of directly graphs that undirected graphs don't have but
无向图没有，但记住这一点，你不能
that undirected graphs don't have but remember this all right you cannot
remember this all right you cannot identify the structure of directed graph
确定有向图的结构加入这个我等效，这是
identify the structure of directed graph join this I equivalent okay and here's
join this I equivalent okay and here's another important definition let's say
另一个重要的定义假设我们有一个分布P好的，让我们
another important definition let's say we have a distribution P okay and let's
we have a distribution P okay and let's define IFP to be the set of independent
将IFP定义为独立于条件独立语句的集合
define IFP to be the set of independent of the condition independent statements
of the condition independent statements implied by the distribution P right
分布P所隐含的权利没有人处境的权利不只是
implied by the distribution P right nobody situation right not just the
nobody situation right not just the distribution P so the story Sultan
分布P所以故事苏丹有条件的独立陈述
distribution P so the story Sultan conditional independent statements we
conditional independent statements we call those I of P now for a given graph
如果G的I是P的I的子集，则立即调用给定图G的P的I
call those I of P now for a given graph G if the I of G is a subset of I of P
G if the I of G is a subset of I of P then we call I agree to be an I map of
那么我们称我同意是分布P的I映射，因此从某种意义上说
then we call I agree to be an I map of the distribution P so in some sense this
the distribution P so in some sense this is the bass work here we can use the
是这里的低音工作，我们可以使用图G作为分布的代理
is the bass work here we can use the graph G as a proxy for the distribution
graph G as a proxy for the distribution P now what you need to keep in mind here
P现在您需要记住的是，分布P可能满足
P now what you need to keep in mind here is that the distribution P may satisfy
is that the distribution P may satisfy additional independent relationships not
不是地面暗示的其他独立关系，而是每个
additional independent relationships not implied by the ground but every
implied by the ground but every independent relation prime where the
独立关系素数，其中图由分布P满足
independent relation prime where the graph is satisfied by the distribution P
graph is satisfied by the distribution P ok that's why the idea here is you can
好的，这就是为什么这里的想法是您可以将其用作安全的Pin代理
ok that's why the idea here is you can use it as a safe proxy for pin actually
use it as a safe proxy for pin actually I'll show you somewhere I don't know
我会告诉你某个地方，我不知道那是一张小照片
I'll show you somewhere I don't know what it is a little picture from
what it is a little picture from Bishop's book but effectively treat this
Bishop的书，但有效地将此G视为允许其通过的过滤器
Bishop's book but effectively treat this G as a filter that allows through it
G as a filter that allows through it only the distributions be the satisfy
只有分布是满足由隐含暗示的独立关系
only the distributions be the satisfy the independence relations implied by
the independence relations implied by the graph okay so if you have a
该图还可以，因此如果您的分布没有
the graph okay so if you have a distribution without
distribution without doesn't describe independence relations
没有描述图的独立关系，所以如果不满足
doesn't describe independence relations of the graph so if this is not satisfied
of the graph so if this is not satisfied then it cannot go through the graph the
如果您不能使用图形工具，那么它就无法通过图的教职员工
then it cannot go through the graph the faculty if you cannot use the graph tool
faculty if you cannot use the graph tool to represent fertilizer distribution so
代表肥料的分布，所以举个例子，让我们来离散
to represent fertilizer distribution so take an example let's take the discrete
take an example let's take the discrete distribution defined selection of Y I
YI的分布定义选择取值0和1，让我们给出一些
distribution defined selection of Y I take values 0 and 1 and let's give some
take values 0 and 1 and let's give some values of the joint probability of the
影响的联合概率的值，以及为什么我不做
values of the joint probability of the effects and why I am NOT going to do the
effects and why I am NOT going to do the algebra you can it's right here assuming
代数你可以在这里，假设计算正确无误，但是
algebra you can it's right here assuming the calculations are correct right but
the calculations are correct right but it comes up that you can show that V of
结果是，您可以证明X到Y的V等于Y的XP的P，所以
it comes up that you can show that V of X to the Y is equal to P of X P of Y so
X to the Y is equal to P of X P of Y so the x and y are marginally independent
x和y几乎是独立的，所以这只小鸡
the x and y are marginally independent all right so the chickens for this
all right so the chickens for this problem is the center don't involve sex
问题是中心不涉及独立于Y的性别好吧这里没有图
problem is the center don't involve sex independent of Y all right no graph here
independent of Y all right no graph here or anything like that right so we have
或类似的权利，所以我们拥有此分布，并且只有
or anything like that right so we have this distribution and the only
this distribution and the only independence relation you can solve is
您可以解决的独立性关系就是您在这里看到的那么高FP
independence relation you can solve is is what you see here so high F P is the
is what you see here so high F P is the set that only includes X independent of
现在只包含独立于Y的X的集合现在让我们考虑不同的图
set that only includes X independent of Y now let's consider different graphs
Y now let's consider different graphs and let's see what is I of G for each of
让我们看看这些图的G的I是多少
and let's see what is I of G for each of these graphs how many independent
these graphs how many independent relations we have here on the left
我们在左边的关系
这个噪声在x和y之间不存在，所以关系是什么
these graphs how many independent relations we have here on the left
this noise exists between x and y nothing so so what is the relation
这个噪声在x和y之间不存在，所以关系是什么
nothing so so what is the relation between x and y independent y FG is
在x和y之间独立y FG包括此类型的包含20x
between x and y independent y FG is include this this type of include 20x
include this this type of include 20x independent Y in this case there is no
在这种情况下，独立Y不存在独立关系0，并且此列表不存在
independent Y in this case there is no independence relation 0 and this list no
independence relation 0 and this list no offense relation is 0 so the agreement
进攻关系为0，因此协议规定所有段落基本上都是您
offense relation is 0 so the agreement made that all paragraphs basically you
made that all paragraphs basically you know they are can be used the surrogates
知道只要有一页，就可以使用它们来代替分布P
know they are can be used the surrogates for the distribution P whenever a page
for the distribution P whenever a page has this property
具有此属性
现在我可以列出这三个图表中的一些来表示
for the distribution P whenever a page has this property
all right now can I list some of these three graphs to represent the
现在我可以列出这三个图表中的一些来表示
three graphs to represent the distribution P this of course because it
分布P这当然是因为它满足时间依赖关系
distribution P this of course because it satisfies the time dependence relation
satisfies the time dependence relation this doesn't require any independence
这不需要任何独立性关系，所以任何分布都可以
this doesn't require any independence relation so any distribution will go
relation so any distribution will go through it the distribution people
通过它分配人，尤其是在额外的独立性方面
through it the distribution people especially in additional independence
especially in additional independence relation but that's okay right
关系，但没关系，您不会在此违反任何规定
relation but that's okay right you will not violate anything in this
you will not violate anything in this graph because this graph gives zero
图，因为该图给出了嵌入的零独立关系，可以
graph because this graph gives zero independence relations embedded okay the
independence relations embedded okay the same in this case so how can we open
在这种情况下也是一样，所以我们如何打开三个图I 1 I 2 I 3等等G的I
same in this case so how can we open three graphs I 1 I 2 I 3 etc the I of G
three graphs I 1 I 2 I 3 etc the I of G is subset the Phi of P so there are I
是P的Phi的子集，所以基本上有P分布的I Maps
is subset the Phi of P so there are I Maps basically of the distribution P
Maps basically of the distribution P alright and if you like a little
好吧，如果您喜欢我所说的话，
alright and if you like a little graphical justification of what I said
graphical justification of what I said before something that we put in red just
之前我们在这里用红色标注的内容，但是由于您只能确定
before something that we put in red just here but since you can only identify
here but since you can only identify graph tracks or apply equivalent alright
图形轨迹或应用等效的方法，所以这是我们的三个入门指南
graph tracks or apply equivalent alright so here are our three starter gets
so here are our three starter gets basically three graphs all right
基本上三张图都可以，你知道我不是
basically three graphs all right and there are you know I not of the
and there are you know I not of the distribution P ok because to blast them
分布P ok是因为炸开它们基本上满足了基础
distribution P ok because to blast them satisfy basically the underlying
satisfy basically the underlying independent relations with pikas
与皮卡斯的独立关系好这是一个
independent relations with pikas ok which is this one
这没什么好说的，所以父母基本上会说这是否真的很正式
this doesn't say anything so a parent basically says if this is really formal
basically says if this is really formal language because already we have paid
语言，因为如果G是，而我是a，那么我们已经带薪休假是十倍
language because already we have paid leave is ten times if G is and I'm a
leave is ten times if G is and I'm a puppy then people priced according to G
幼犬，然后人们按照G定价，然后按照G受精
puppy then people priced according to G okay and fertilized according to G
okay and fertilized according to G basically implies this authorization
基本上意味着我们迄今为止所看到的这种授权，并且
basically implies this authorization that we have seen up to now and the
that we have seen up to now and the proof is sort of trivial because if you
证明是微不足道的，因为如果采用分布P并安排
proof is sort of trivial because if you take the distribution P and you arrange
take the distribution P and you arrange the nodes in topological order using
使用某种概率的乘积规则按拓扑顺序排列节点
the nodes in topological order using sort of the product rules of probability
sort of the product rules of probability you can write it as you see on the first
您可以像在第一行中看到的那样编写它，或者总是在这里生病然后
you can write it as you see on the first line or always be sick here and then
line or always be sick here and then these previous notes will be basically
这些以前的音符基本上将是
these previous notes will be basically the parent and the known descendants to
the parent and the known descendants to accept the pilot so Z is the non
接受飞行员，所以Z是非后代-父母和我可以写
accept the pilot so Z is the non descendants - the parent and I can write
descendants - the parent and I can write this probability equal to that Y because
这个概率等于Y，因为G是P的I，并且有
this probability equal to that Y because G is an I'm up of P and there is the
G is an I'm up of P and there is the proof of the fear all right Z is an IMAP
恐惧的证明，好吧Z是T ok的IMAP
proof of the fear all right Z is an IMAP of T ok
of T ok then P Papa Hodges according to C so
然后P Papa Hodges根据C，所以基本上的想法是，如果这满足
then P Papa Hodges according to C so basically the idea is if this satisfies
basically the idea is if this satisfies the independence relations implied by
然后，上帝暗示的独立关系就达到顶峰，并受精于
the independence relations implied by the God then peak and fertilized on the
the God then peak and fertilized on the graph the way we have seen it which is
以我们看到的方式绘制图表，这没关系，因此再也没有什么特别的
graph the way we have seen it which is this ok so again nothing extraordinary
this ok so again nothing extraordinary we have seen this ten times but the
我们已经看过十次了，但是第一次是总共四次，只需要
we have seen this ten times but the first is total four it only requires
first is total four it only requires this property of conditional
图Z和B隐含的条件独立性的这一特性
this property of conditional independence implied by the graph Z and
independence implied by the graph Z and this is what I have used okay now if you
这是我现在使用的，如果您权衡一下，我认为可能是
this is what I have used okay now if you weigh around and I think it may be
weigh around and I think it may be coming in a few slides I won't cover
来几张幻灯片，我不会介绍，但是如果您想开始
coming in a few slides I won't cover that but if you want to start with
that but if you want to start with ition that but for a sizzler gratin you
的意思是，但对于一个嘶哑的烤焦干酪，您想证明独立关系，例如
ition that but for a sizzler gratin you want to prove independence relation such
want to prove independence relation such as based equal to that if you can
等于等于如果您实际上可以直接通过类似于
as based equal to that if you can actually do directly by similar to the
actually do directly by similar to the examples we developed three lectures
我们开发了三个讲座的例子，所以您可以谈论
examples we developed three lectures okay so you can just talk about
okay so you can just talk about distribution compute this and then
分布计算这个，然后Sullivan等于那个就可以了
distribution compute this and then Sullivan is equal to that all right this
Sullivan is equal to that all right this is just the example we discussed we have
只是我们讨论过的例子，我们已经看到这没有必要了
is just the example we discussed we have seen this no need
seen this no need okay definition many definitions here
好的定义这里有很多定义并没有什么特别令人惊奇的
okay definition many definitions here nothing really amazing so with the
nothing really amazing so with the current ago being an IMAP for the
当前是分配的IMAP，所以现在我将定义
current ago being an IMAP for the distribution right so now I will define
distribution right so now I will define it to be a line and a graph is a minimal
如果去除甚至一个线，它就是一条线和一个图是一个最小的IMAP井。
it to be a line and a graph is a minimal IMAP well if the removal of even a
IMAP well if the removal of even a single edge from the graph when the
当街道不是分布的地图时，从图的单边开始
single edge from the graph when the street not a map of the distribution in
street not a map of the distribution in other ways there is not a step set of Z
其他方法没有Z的步进集，使得Z素数为P的IMAP可以
other ways there is not a step set of Z such that Z prime is an IMAP of P okay
such that Z prime is an IMAP of P okay so that we call it the name a Lima
所以我们称它为利马这个名字，而我想做的最后一件事
so that we call it the name a Lima alright and the last thing I want to
alright and the last thing I want to define is the Osher this is the graph of
定义是Osher，这是告诉您的图表
define is the Osher this is the graph of was telling you with which is
was telling you with which is pictorially a nice way to think of this
以图形化的方式思考这个问题的正确方法，我对此进行了正确的映射，因此该学科具有
pictorially a nice way to think of this I maps right so the discipline has a
I maps right so the discipline has a distribution to pass through all right
当分配满足条件时，分配通过所有权利
distribution to pass through all right when the distribution satisfies the
when the distribution satisfies the independence relations implied by the
图所隐含的独立关系，但分布P可以具有
independence relations implied by the graph but the distribution P can have
graph but the distribution P can have additional independence relations not
图的权利未暗示其他独立关系，但无论如何
additional independence relations not implied by the graph right but whatever
implied by the graph right but whatever is implied by the graph has to be
由图隐含必须由分布来满足
is implied by the graph has to be satisfied by the distribution otherwise
satisfied by the distribution otherwise this doesn't pass through that's why you
这没有通过，这就是为什么您知道这里的概念是因为您使用的是
this doesn't pass through that's why you know the concept here is you use this is
know the concept here is you use this is a distribution filter
分配过滤器很好，我告诉我带来最后一对
a distribution filter well I tell me bring the last pair
well I tell me bring the last pair another complicated actually concept we
我们将通过另一个非常基本的概念获得另一个复杂的实际概念
another complicated actually concept we will get with one very fundamental
will get with one very fundamental example so if somebody gives you a
例如，如果有人给您分配了许多变量的分布P，您可以
example so if somebody gives you a distribution P of many variables can you
distribution P of many variables can you find the directed graph that has exactly
查找具有完全相同的独立关系条件的有向图
find the directed graph that has exactly the same independent relations condition
the same independent relations condition independent relations as the
独立的关系，因为分布P P不可能
independent relations as the distribution P the P is not possible you
distribution P the P is not possible you can write down some winner distribution
可以写下一些具有条件独立性的获胜者分布
can write down some winner distribution with some conditional independence
with some conditional independence relation can you find a graph that is
关系，您可以找到基本上是该图的理想图的图吗？
relation can you find a graph that is basically a perfect map of the
basically a perfect map of the distribution this is what I call a
分布这就是我所说的完美地图
distribution this is what I call a perfect map
我的意思是，您可以欣赏这种类型的功能吗？
I mean you can can you appreciate that this type of is a little bit more
this type of is a little bit more difficult problem than before if one is
比以前困难的问题，如果你是一个图形，你说好吧，我知道
difficult problem than before if one is you make a graph and you say okay I know
you make a graph and you say okay I know what relations are satisfied
满足什么关系，所以我知道哪个分布
what relations are satisfied so I know which distributions which
so I know which distributions which let's find out now you were given a
现在让我们找出分配P，然后说可以找到
let's find out now you were given a distribution P and you say can you find
distribution P and you say can you find me a graph that represents the
我的图表可以很好地代表分布，所以
me a graph that represents the distribution precisely okay so the
distribution precisely okay so the answer is not every distribution has a
答案不是每个发行版都有完美的地图和非常基础的
answer is not every distribution has a perfect map and a very fundamental
perfect map and a very fundamental example in the literature you will love
在文学中的例子，您会喜欢指向许多实际致力于的页面
example in the literature you will love point many pages devoted actually to
point many pages devoted actually to this example is an example with four
这个例子是一个有四个变量的例子，这是一个无向的
this example is an example with four variables this is the an undirected
variables this is the an undirected version of the graph that satisfies the
使用依赖关系满足以下关系的图的版本
version of the graph that satisfies the following relation using dependency
following relation using dependency given B and D and this independent of B
给定B和D，而这个独立于B的给定FC的方式是，自
given B and D and this independent of B given a FC by the way that since the
given a FC by the way that since the biggest bottleneck in principle is
原则上最大的瓶颈在于成为插值算法
biggest bottleneck in principle is become interpolation algorithm in in
become interpolation algorithm in in undirected graphs you may want to
无向图，您可能想了解这里的路径，但是当它们
undirected graphs you may want to appreciate the path here but when they
appreciate the path here but when they are independent given a and T and a and
在给定a和T的情况下是独立的，而在给定D和B的情况下，a和C是独立的，因为
are independent given a and T and a and C are independent given D and B because
C are independent given D and B because in essence the let's say aliens here
本质上，我们可以说，给定T和B的外星人是独立的，因为
in essence the let's say aliens here independent given T and B because the
independent given T and B because the path from A to C is blocked if you go
如果您以这种方式从A到C的路径被阻止，则将其移出则称为“阻止”
path from A to C is blocked if you go this way call it block if you move out
this way call it block if you move out way given D and B okay so the separation
给定D和B的方式好吧，所以分离实际上就是我们这样的分离
way given D and B okay so the separation is really this separation the way we
is really this separation the way we have said in directed graphs but this
已经在有向图中说过，但是这个无向图满足这种关系
have said in directed graphs but this undirected graph satisfies this relation
undirected graph satisfies this relation okay this can you pass me that the
好吧，这可以告诉我最大的一个吗
okay this can you pass me that the biggest one out which basically it
biggest one out which basically it doesn't care care about arrows or
不在乎箭头或其他任何东西，如果您知道您给了他们B
doesn't care care about arrows or anything if the you know you give them B
anything if the you know you give them B then this path is blocked then this path
然后这条路被封锁然后这条路被封锁
then this path is blocked then this path is blocked
is blocked okay if you're given a and T and you
好吧，如果给定a和T，并且您想转到这两个路径，
okay if you're given a and T and you want to go to these the two paths are
want to go to these the two paths are also blocked so this have the relations
也被阻止，所以这有关系，所以您要问的是我能找到
also blocked so this have the relations and so you're asking is can I find the
and so you're asking is can I find the directed graph that actually satisfies
实际满足这两个关系的有向图
directed graph that actually satisfies these two relations
these two relations and this and so here are two examples
这就是这两个例子尽管有两个
and this and so here are two examples this examples have despite its two
this examples have despite its two relation what do you think
关系你怎么看
我的意思是你可以知道，我会说这实际上是你花了10分钟
this examples have despite its two relation what do you think
I mean you can you know and I would say this actually you spend maybe 10 minutes
我的意思是你可以知道，我会说这实际上是你花了10分钟
this actually you spend maybe 10 minutes to prove if this to the lessons are
证明这些图表是否满足本课程的要求，但请看一下
to prove if this to the lessons are satisfied by these graphs but just look
satisfied by these graphs but just look at it visually are this two graphs
从视觉上看，这两个图基本上具有相同的独立
at it visually are this two graphs basically having the same independent
basically having the same independent relation says this undirected graph so
关系说这个无向图，所以它在这里说，所以我们说这个图
relation says this undirected graph so it says here so let's say this graph
it says here so let's say this graph right which is being dependent on this
对，这取决于此图最大的部分是什么
right which is being dependent on this graph what is the part of the biggest
graph what is the part of the biggest algorithm of Facebook based independent
基于Facebook的D独立算法，无条件，无条件，是
algorithm of Facebook based independent of D with no conditioning nothing is
of D with no conditioning nothing is given right here right there's no
在这里给出的权利没有证据，所以这是没有条件的，
given right here right there's no evidence so that is no condition and the
evidence so that is no condition and the goal from B to D the only ways to go
目标从B到D的唯一途径是什么
goal from B to D the only ways to go through there and what is this is the
through there and what is this is the best marks right this is the explaining
最好的评分对，这是父母这次基本上造成的解释
best marks right this is the explaining away this time parents basically causes
away this time parents basically causes of the same the factory so basically
同一家工厂，所以基本上，因为这甚至不是他们的博客
of the same the factory so basically since this is not even being their blog
since this is not even being their blog though they are independent okay
尽管他们是独立的，所以这种关系与
though they are independent okay so this relation has nothing to do with
so this relation has nothing to do with any of Austria's similarly BN one does
奥地利的任何一个类似国阵的人基本上都不满足这两个条件
any of Austria's similarly BN one does not satisfy basically those two
not satisfy basically those two relations so bottom line
关系，因此底线不是每个分布都有一个完美的
relations so bottom line not every distribution has a perfect
not every distribution has a perfect mark okay so don't expect to basically
标记好吧，所以不要指望基本上有分布然后撒
mark okay so don't expect to basically have a distribution and then sprinkle
have a distribution and then sprinkle the graph that represents it usually you
代表它的图通常从带有一些图的图开始
the graph that represents it usually you start with a graph with some
start with a graph with some mathematical intuition and then you use
数学直觉，然后将图形用作图形的代理
mathematical intuition and then you use the graph as a proxy for the
the graph as a proxy for the distributions you want to to work with
您想使用它的发行版，但是这样做的想法是
distributions you want to to work with it but the idea to do that is if you are
it but the idea to do that is if you are limiting yourself to the distributions
将自己限制在满足我们图的性质的分布上
limiting yourself to the distributions of satisfies the properties of our graph
of satisfies the properties of our graph anything else basically
其他基本上可以使用的东西看起来都不像
anything else basically working with it's not look like a
working with it's not look like a mathematical model and you are have to
数学模型，您必须遵守该模型的规则，如果
mathematical model and you are have to obey the rules of that model and if the
obey the rules of that model and if the model is wrong you have problems all
模型是错误的，您有问题没关系的基本上是
model is wrong you have problems all right don't need was to basically
right don't need was to basically they're repeating project part so next
他们正在重复项目的一部分，所以下一次去今天的极限
they're repeating project part so next time go to the limits for today
讲座没有发布没有时间
the lecture is not being posted didn't have time
they have time to have lots of drink my coffee so this is priority number six
他们有时间喝很多我的咖啡，所以这是第六要务
coffee so this is priority number six okay so you'll be there by later today
好吧，今天晚些时候你会在那里
因此，有效地推断办公室意味着正确，但我们提供了一些建议
coffee so this is priority number six okay so you'll be there by later today
so inferencing the office effectively means right but we are giving some
因此，有效地推断办公室意味着正确，但我们提供了一些建议
means right but we are giving some evidence and we have to estimate some
证据，我们必须估计一些未知量，可以是
evidence and we have to estimate some unknown quantities which can be either
unknown quantities which can be either the student variables and and we do lots
学生变量，并且我们做了很多例子，基本上是隐藏变量
the student variables and and we do lots of examples basically hidden variables
of examples basically hidden variables would be one for each data point but
每个数据点一个，但也有很多静态参数
would be one for each data point but also will be lots of static parameters
also will be lots of static parameters like the parameters in the conditional
就像我们需要做的条件分布中的参数一样
like the parameters in the conditional distributions that we need just made so
distributions that we need just made so that's an interest problem okay for
这是一个有趣的问题，例如在我们隐藏的马尔可夫模型中
that's an interest problem okay for example in hidden Markov models that we
example in hidden Markov models that we will spend maybe two lectures to to go
可能要花两堂课来讲解您刚刚制作的细节
will spend maybe two lectures to to go through the details you just made the
through the details you just made the hidden states if you've given the
隐藏状态，如果您已经对技术进行了观察
hidden states if you've given the technology observations okay in for
technology observations okay in for example in disease-causing I'm sorry in
例如，在致病中，例如，在对称应用中，我很抱歉
example in disease-causing I'm sorry in in symmetrical applications for example
in symmetrical applications for example did you know the some symptoms that the
您知道患者有哪些症状吗？您在问什么
did you know the some symptoms that the patient has and you are asking what is
patient has and you are asking what is the disease that causes those symptoms
导致这些症状的疾病还可以，所以基本上与
the disease that causes those symptoms okay so it's basically the same thing as
okay so it's basically the same thing as in hmm but the variables some of them
以hmm为单位，但是其中一些变量可以是连续的或离散的
in hmm but the variables some of them can be continuous or discrete
can be continuous or discrete so some mixing with state-space models
因此可能会与状态空​​间模型进行某些混合，还有许多其他情况
so some mixing with state-space models may be the case and there's many other
may be the case and there's many other examples as well so the equation that we
也有一些例子，所以我们讨论的方程式基本上就是这个方程式
examples as well so the equation that we discussed is basically this equation
discussed is basically this equation that you see here and I'm going to do a
你在这里看到的，今天我将做一个非常具体的例子
that you see here and I'm going to do a very specific example today with
very specific example today with discrete variables hopefully before the
希望在讲座结束前使用离散变量，以便您可以看到
discrete variables hopefully before the end of the lecture so you can see this
end of the lecture so you can see this equation in action
等式在起作用，所以这里的符号是
equation in action so here the notation this is the
so here the notation this is the evidence V means visible variable states
证据V表示可见的变量状态，表明隐藏的脚是静态的
evidence V means visible variable states that hidden feet are the static
that hidden feet are the static parameters like that the distributions
像这样的参数定义概率表的分布
parameters like that the distributions defining the probability tables
您基本上是这样写联合分配的，这是
you basically write the Joint Distribution like that and this is the
Distribution like that and this is the evidence and the evidence basically
证据，而证据基本上要求对隐藏的事物进行边缘化
evidence and the evidence basically requires marginalization over the hidden
requires marginalization over the hidden variables as you see on the bottom and
变量，如您在底部看到的，这是三个示例
variables as you see on the bottom and and these are the three examples
and these are the three examples basically that you know or two of the
基本上，您知道解放的两个例子，所以这是
basically that you know or two of the examples of liberation so this is the
examples of liberation so this is the kind of operations we need to do and you
我们需要做的那种操作，您会注意到这里有一个很大的汇总
kind of operations we need to do and you notice here there is a big summation so
notice here there is a big summation so if these variables are hundreds of
如果这些变量是成千上万，如果您需要在筏子中执行此操作
if these variables are hundreds of thousands if you need to do this in raft
thousands if you need to do this in raft in a very effective way all right
以一种非常有效的方式，否则这个计算将是
in a very effective way all right otherwise this calculation would be
otherwise this calculation would be computationally sort of not easy thing
计算上不容易做的事
computationally sort of not easy thing to do
to do okay so don't get the impression or the
好吧，所以不要得到印象或总和X是，但是我们说它是
okay so don't get the impression or the summation and X a yes but let's say it's
summation and X a yes but let's say it's exhales its thousand variables and each
呼出它的一千个变量，每个变量取十个值，然后
exhales its thousand variables and each of them takes ten values then you're in
of them takes ten values then you're in trouble
麻烦好喷头问题的网络图是
trouble okay sprinkler problem the web graph is
okay sprinkler problem the web graph is the visible variables right so W is the
可见变量正确，所以W是变量，隐藏变量是
the visible variables right so W is the variables the hidden variables is let's
variables the hidden variables is let's say in this particular case we're
说在这种情况下，我们很想知道洒水装置是
say in this particular case we're interested to know it the sprinkler is
interested to know it the sprinkler is on or okay and they call them here
继续，还是可以的，他们在某种意义上称它们为讨厌的变量，但我
on or okay and they call them here nuisance variables in the sense but I
nuisance variables in the sense but I only want to estimate if the sprinkler
只想估算洒水器是否全错我并不在乎
only want to estimate if the sprinkler is all wrong I don't really care about
is all wrong I don't really care about the Claudian array so there are hidden
克劳迪安阵列，所以有隐藏的底部被列出，因为我没有兴趣
the Claudian array so there are hidden bottom is listed as I have no interest
bottom is listed as I have no interest to the estimation and if you have no
进行估算，如果您对估算没有兴趣，那么您会知道自己
to the estimation and if you have no interest in estimation you know what you
interest in estimation you know what you need to do with them you need to
需要与他们合作，您需要将它们整合到一起
need to do with them you need to integrate them out by that's the
integrate them out by that's the Bayesian way okay so again this T naught
贝叶斯方法还可以，所以这又是什么，他们真的是隐藏变量
Bayesian way okay so again this T naught and s they're really hidden variables
and s they're really hidden variables but in this case they only care involved
但是在这种情况下，他们只在乎洒水喷头，所以这就是
but in this case they only care involved the sprinkler so this is where there are
the sprinkler so this is where there are called my query or hidden variables this
叫我的查询或隐藏变量，这又被隐藏了，不在乎，所以我
called my query or hidden variables this again are hidden by was don't care so I
again are hidden by was don't care so I am going to
将要-很棒的他们，你可以看到
am going to - great them out and you can see the
- great them out and you can see the integration out on CNR so when I write
积分在CNR上，所以当我写这个时s和W的联合概率
integration out on CNR so when I write this the joint probability of s and W
this the joint probability of s and W divided by the probability of W you
除以您在分母中注意到的W的概率，因为我有
divided by the probability of W you notice in the denominator since I have
notice in the denominator since I have the joint of all the variables i
我边缘化的所有变量的联合将是
the joint of all the variables i marginalize this would be the
marginalize this would be the probability of love you shall have to
爱的概率，您将必须多重依赖于C和R
probability of love you shall have to multi relies on s C and R on the
multi relies on s C and R on the numerator this is the join of S&amp;W
分子这是S＆W的联接S＆W必须与边缘化
numerator this is the join of S&amp;W S&amp;W shall have to marginalize with
S&amp;W shall have to marginalize with respects to these notions variables
对这些概念的尊重阴天和雨天，这就是你所看到的
respects to these notions variables cloudy and rain and this is what you see
cloudy and rain and this is what you see here okay
在这里，您可以开始进行这些现代化改造
here okay these modernisations you can start off
these modernisations you can start off think you know visually at least in the
认为您至少在离散变量s的上下文中在视觉上知道一些
think you know visually at least in the context of discrete variables s as some
context of discrete variables s as some sort of collapsing big tables so you can
那种折叠的大桌子，所以如果您有一个XYZ桌子
sort of collapsing big tables so you can take care if you have an XYZ table that
take care if you have an XYZ table that the speed of a pie with numbers all
一个数字的馅饼速度很好，所以每个小小的爱盒
the speed of a pie with numbers all right so each of this little love boxes
right so each of this little love boxes the cubes contains the probability of x
多维数据集包含x y＆z在此具有特定值的概率
the cubes contains the probability of x y&amp;z having the particular values in this
y&amp;z having the particular values in this box right so if you want from this to
右边的方框，这样，如果您想从中获得有吸引力的边际收益，您可以
box right so if you want from this to get the marginal attractively you can be
get the marginal attractively you can be conception in the direction of Z to get
沿Z方向构想以获得二维工作台的右斜率
conception in the direction of Z to get the two-dimensional table right slope
the two-dimensional table right slope this which is easily processed in two
如果是五十维，则很容易在二维中处理
this which is easily processed in two dimensions if it is in fifty dimensions
dimensions if it is in fifty dimensions really performing all these summations
真正执行所有这些求和是一项艰巨的任务，好吧，所以
really performing all these summations it's a if they're expensive task okay so
it's a if they're expensive task okay so keep that in mind
记在脑子里
所以再次针对这个特殊情况可能会让您知道一些
it's a if they're expensive task okay so keep that in mind
so again for this particular probably might give you you know some of the
所以再次针对这个特殊情况可能会让您知道一些
might give you you know some of the calculations I think they were contained
我认为这些计算也包含在上一张幻灯片中，因此
calculations I think they were contained also in the previous slide so
also in the previous slide so effectively what you do is you plug in
有效地做的是插入变量的联合分布
effectively what you do is you plug in the Joint Distribution of the variables
the Joint Distribution of the variables you plug in the values of s and W that
您插入您感兴趣的s和W的值，然后您必须
you plug in the values of s and W that your of interest and then you have to
your of interest and then you have to sum over all the possible values of
将这些阴天和雨的所有可能值相加
sum over all the possible values of these cloudy and rain
these cloudy and rain so this summations each of these
因此，这些求和值每个都取两个值的总和
so this summations each of these variables which say takes two values all
variables which say takes two values all along so you're going to have terms that
这样，您将拥有与这四个词一样大的术语，
along so you're going to have terms that are as big as this so four terms and
are as big as this so four terms and then I feel you're gonna have eight
那我觉得你会有八个词，所以一般来说
then I feel you're gonna have eight terms so generally if the body of this
terms so generally if the body of this table if the favors are obviously the
如果青睐显然是当前离散变量的表，那是一个非常
table if the favors are obviously the present discrete variables that's a very
present discrete variables that's a very easy problem all right
容易的问题好多年解决了一个问题
easy problem all right there is a problem solved out the years
there is a problem solved out the years ago so there's really no interest to do
以前所以真的没有兴趣进行任何研究，然后您就可以了
ago so there's really no interest to do any research right then you take this
any research right then you take this because the money curves except in our
因为除了现在的情节以外，货币曲线至少现在分布
because the money curves except in our plot right now at least distributions
plot right now at least distributions are sort of forgotten I want to believe
有点被遗忘了我想相信所有事情都已经完成了
are sort of forgotten I want to believe that everything has been done also
that everything has been done also thirty forty years ago
三十四十年了，所以没有什么不只是为了
thirty forty years ago okay so there's nothing no it's just to
okay so there's nothing no it's just to do if these conditional distributions
如果这些条件分布是指数族I的成员，该怎么办
do if these conditional distributions are members of the exponential family I
are members of the exponential family I think the things you already have been
认为你已经做过的事情，看起来不怎么好
think the things you already have been done and they don't look very much
done and they don't look very much different from working with gaussians
与那些不知道什么是高斯的人和高斯人一起工作的方式不同
different from working with gaussians for those who don't know what's an
for those who don't know what's an exponential family of distributions you
指数分布族，您可能想从
exponential family of distributions you may want to look on my slice from the
may want to look on my slice from the first in the previous semester and just
上学期的第一个，只是一个漂亮的表格示例，但告诉您
first in the previous semester and just the sample a nice table but tells you
the sample a nice table but tells you which distribution speak you know
您知道哪种分布类型您知道类别，以及为什么我们做的很好
which distribution speak you know category and why things are nice when we
category and why things are nice when we work with that but right now I mean a
与之合作，但现在我是说底特律是我们最基础的单位
work with that but right now I mean a Detroit's our most basic unit with
Detroit's our most basic unit with discrete values and Gaussian to convey
离散值和高斯基本传达了如何操作的信息
discrete values and Gaussian to convey the message basically on how to operate
the message basically on how to operate with this graph
这张图，所以让我们从离散动物开始，如果
with this graph so let's start with discrete animals if
so let's start with discrete animals if something doesn't make sense to stop me
没有什么可以阻止我的，因为这种例子是
something doesn't make sense to stop me because this sort of this examples were
because this sort of this examples were built on lots more complicated graphs as
在我们学习过程中建立在许多更复杂的图形上，所以让我说
built on lots more complicated graphs as we go along in the course so let's say I
we go along in the course so let's say I have two discrete variables X 1 and X 2
有两个离散变量X 1和X 2，它们形成了一个多诺丽分布
have two discrete variables X 1 and X 2 and they form a multi noni distribution
and they form a multi noni distribution so they can take each of them can take
因此他们可以接受每个人可以接受不同的值
so they can take each of them can take take different values each of these
take different values each of these values with probability mu I for the sum
持有总和的概率为mu I的值等于R，因此您可以
values with probability mu I for the sum of holding is equal to R so you can
of holding is equal to R so you can think you know this is a generalization
想想你知道这是一个二进制值的概括，我可以取值0
think you know this is a generalization of a binary value me I can take values 0
of a binary value me I can take values 0 1 here I can take 10 values each of
1在这里，我可以取10个值中的每个值，以亩为单位
1 here I can take 10 values each of those values with probability mu army to
those values with probability mu army to UK okay so there are two cases if the
英国好吧，所以有两种情况，如果最笼统的是写联合
UK okay so there are two cases if the most general will be to write the Joint
most general will be to write the Joint Distribution the way that you see here
分发您在此处看到的方式，对于此处不熟悉的符号都可以
Distribution the way that you see here okay for both not familiar notation here
okay for both not familiar notation here this axis right on 0 1 alright so we
这个轴在0 1上正确，所以我们发送了每个植物学家，但是这个身体
this axis right on 0 1 alright so we send each of the botanist but this body
send each of the botanist but this body was to take with probabilities mu i all
我要带着概率我可以
was to take with probabilities mu i all right
right is the only one but you don't know which
是唯一的一个，但是您不知道K个变量中的哪个处于活动状态，所以我们
is the only one but you don't know which of the K variables is active so what we
of the K variables is active so what we do here you notice is this is the joint
在这里您会注意到这是联合分布的概率
do here you notice is this is the joint distribution the probability of this
distribution the probability of this take the value I and still manage the
取值I并仍管理排除theta值J，我们称之为V IJ
take the value I and still manage the exclude theta value J we call it V IJ
exclude theta value J we call it V IJ right so this is the joint probability
是的，所以这是在此仅具有值R的联合概率
right so this is the joint probability that this just has the value R in this
that this just has the value R in this case the body J and I put in the
情况下，主体J和我今天放入指数X 1 IX，我将
case the body J and I put in the exponent X 1 IX today and I take the
exponent X 1 IX today and I take the part of a forecast massage Sanjay
Sanjay预测按摩的一部分，因为在此产品中，只有任务I
part of a forecast massage Sanjay because in this product only mission I
because in this product only mission I and one terry from X 1 and X 2 will take
X 1和X 2的一个毛圈将取值为1，其他所有取值为
and one terry from X 1 and X 2 will take the value 1 and everything else will be
the value 1 and everything else will be 0 right and something preserving did you
0对，您做了些保留的工作
0 right and something preserving did you work
work you are alright because the various
您没事，因为各种效果都是正确的，所以如果我们去
you are alright because the various effects the star right so if we went to
effects the star right so if we went to a like this this is the only way we can
像这样，这是我们可以做到的唯一方法之一，每个晚上的距离
a like this this is the only way we can do it one of the night distance a each
do it one of the night distance a each vector r1 is equal to 1 this equal to
向量r1等于1等于市场x12等于等于等于
vector r1 is equal to 1 this equal to market x12 equal to that than equal to
market x12 equal to that than equal to that because we were run out of paper
那是因为我们没纸了
that because we were run out of paper okay
okay this equation is compact it works you
这个方程很紧凑，可以为您提供联合概率分布mu IJ
this equation is compact it works you the joint probability distribution mu IJ
the joint probability distribution mu IJ and you isolate God
然后你将上帝隔离了，所以这就是你所知道的，
and you isolate God okay so this is you know it says the
okay so this is you know it says the number of counts that parameters in this
这个波兰语k步长中的参数的计数数量将是
number of counts that parameters in this polish k square- walk will will be this
polish k square- walk will will be this number control
号码控制
所以我们有K平方，那么一个来自四边形
polish k square- walk will will be this number control
so we have K squared then the one comes from quad
所以kmkj广场，一个来自
so kmkj square and the one comes from
密码为什么是一个密码
what's the password why one there's one there
不
nope
因为当我写所有可能的概率时，您就知道了
because when I some write all the possible probabilities the you know of
possible probabilities the you know of the different states the sum has to be
不同状态的总和必须等于1是归一化先生K
the different states the sum has to be equal to one is a normalization sir K
equal to one is a normalization sir K square minus one right now if I assume
如果我假设X 1和X 2的分布，则现在减去1
square minus one right now if I assume that the distributions of X 1 and X 2
that the distributions of X 1 and X 2 are independent given the parameters
是独立的，给定参数意味着我可以写而不是重复
are independent given the parameters mean I can write instead of repeating
mean I can write instead of repeating this with this joint probabilities mean
这个具有联合概率的意思是说我可以将其写为
this with this joint probabilities mean say I can write this as the progress of
say I can write this as the progress of UI's times the product of u j's
UI乘以u j的乘积的乘积，这就是我写的方式
UI's times the product of u j's okay and here the way it is written I am
okay and here the way it is written I am assuming that mu is the same basically
假设亩基本上与x1 x2相同，好吧，我什么也没看到
assuming that mu is the same basically about x1 x2 okay I don't see anything
about x1 x2 okay I don't see anything that separates the two so right they are
这样就将两者分开了，所以它们是独立的，特别是
that separates the two so right they are independent and particularly way the
independent and particularly way the circle I'm going to tell you in a circle
我要围成一圈告诉你
让我们指望没有发布支持，然后我们将讨论这是什么
independent and particularly way the circle I'm going to tell you in a circle
let's count to support is not released and then we will discuss what this is
让我们指望没有发布支持，然后我们将讨论这是什么
and then we will discuss what this is about
关于210减去r的流量
about what is the 210 minus r oncoming flow to
what is the 210 minus r oncoming flow to describe each of this distribution sorry
请描述每个分布，抱歉，因为这是两个分布的乘积
describe each of this distribution sorry because this is the product of two
because this is the product of two independent solutions of x1 x2 how many
x1 x2的独立解决方案每个参数需要多少个参数值
independent solutions of x1 x2 how many values from a parameter need for each of
values from a parameter need for each of this individual product terms and it
这个单独的产品条款，现在十年来就减了一个
this individual product terms and it came minus one right here 10 years
came minus one right here 10 years normalization of each of the P of x1 pfx
对x1 pfx的每个P进行归一化，这样k减去1，然后我得到两个
normalization of each of the P of x1 pfx do so k minus 1 and then I have two
do so k minus 1 and then I have two blocks so the new essentially means that
阻止，所以新的本质上意味着当我拥有它时，符号尚不清楚
blocks so the new essentially means that when I have it the notation is not clear
when I have it the notation is not clear of saying that chuan has it song lyrics
说到chuan拥有自己的歌词，你会发现
of saying that chuan has it song lyrics to has its own new you see that
是的
yes No
所以基本上这个原理是一样的所以x1可以取一个状态
so basically this works the same is this equation right so x1 can take a states
equation right so x1 can take a states each of this case 2 I is with four
在这种情况下，每个案例2我都有4个提交对象，所以我们说
each of this case 2 I is with four committed in the I so let's say for
committed in the I so let's say for example that this was a mining anything
例如，这是在附近土地上采矿的任何东西，那么它将是
example that this was a mining anything right so near land it would be the
right so near land it would be the probability of x1 is during minute 2
x1的概率在2分钟内，即1减去b1，即概率
probability of x1 is during minute 2 which is 1 minus b1 that the probability
which is 1 minus b1 that the probability equal to 1 but Sarah have a of those
等于1，但是莎拉（Sarah）处于那个阶段，所以我喜欢所有人
equal to 1 but Sarah have a of those stage so I like all of them like that
stage so I like all of them like that and because I have K State's and K news
因为我有K State和K新闻，所以我们必须要某人，所以我真的有
and because I have K State's and K news they we have to someone so I really have
they we have to someone so I really have K minus 1 K minus 1 parameters okay so I
K减1 K减1参数好，所以我有K减十二参数
K minus 1 K minus 1 parameters okay so I have K minus twelve parameter the
have K minus twelve parameter the implication is that this term use are
含义是，此词的用法现在有所不同，所以这是正确的，所以
implication is that this term use are different now this is a thing right so
different now this is a thing right so you know this year I you know for
你知道今年，你知道这个独立的例子
you know this year I you know for example for this independent
example for this independent distribution have it like that if you
如果您有LM的一般发行版，则具有类似的发行版
distribution have it like that if you have a general distribution of LM
have a general distribution of LM variables basically the total number of
变量基本上参数的总数是K到N减去1全部
variables basically the total number of parameters is K to the N minus 1 all
parameters is K to the N minus 1 all right this is similar to what we had
对，这类似于我们在这里拥有的，所以我们有两个值k square-
right this is similar to what we had here so we have two values k square-
here so we have two values k square- want for them to be K to the M minus 1
希望他们是K到M减去1，所以对于实际来说这太快了
want for them to be K to the M minus 1 so this is gross too fast for actually
so this is gross too fast for actually being able to do anything
如果值是独立的，则现在可以执行任何操作
being able to do anything now if the values are independent the
now if the values are independent the novel problem should be K minus 1 for
新问题的分布时间M应该为K减1，因此非常小
novel problem should be K minus 1 for its distribution times M so very small
its distribution times M so very small number and if I have a Markov chain
数字，如果我有一个马尔可夫链，其中所有内容都定义在
number and if I have a Markov chain alright where everything is defined in
alright where everything is defined in terms of this conditional distributions
X i的该条件分布的项仅给出了先前的值，因此
terms of this conditional distributions of X i given only the previous value so
of X i given only the previous value so this is a first-order Markov chain it
这是一阶马尔可夫链，表示参数总数
this is a first-order Markov chain it says that the total number of parameters
says that the total number of parameters is K minus 1 plus n minus 1 K K minus 1
是K减1加n减1 KK减1，然后告诉我它在那说什么
is K minus 1 plus n minus 1 K K minus 1 and and tell me what it says there what
and and tell me what it says there what is this novel comic problem so if I have
是这个新颖的漫画问题，所以如果我有一个马尔可夫链，那么一阶宽
is this novel comic problem so if I have a Markov chain a first-order wide the
a Markov chain a first-order wide the total number of parameters for you know
您知道的参数总数是我的变量是K减去1加M减去1
total number of parameters for you know my variables is K minus 1 plus M minus 1
my variables is K minus 1 plus M minus 1 K minus 1 J minus 1 is from you remember
K减1 J减1来自您记得描述您的联合分布
K minus 1 J minus 1 is from you remember to describe the Joint Distribution you
to describe the Joint Distribution you need to start with P of x1 and then P of
需要以x1的P开头，然后X的P将给出下一个100 P或给定的53
need to start with P of x1 and then P of X will give the next 100 P or 53 given
X will give the next 100 P or 53 given x2 etc so P reflects one has K minus
x2等等，所以P反映了一个K减去它在哪里的小变量，然后我
x2 etc so P reflects one has K minus small variables where it is and then I
small variables where it is and then I have remaining n minus 1 particles and
有剩余的n减去1个粒子，它们是通过此定义的
have remaining n minus 1 particles and they are defined through this
they are defined through this conditional distribution and how much
有条件的分配以及在这种情况下我需要多少个身体
conditional distribution and how much how many body must I need for this case
how many body must I need for this case here and K any K square minus K because
这里，K是任何K平方减去K，因为这种分布具有许多影响，我
here and K any K square minus K because this distribution for its many effects I
this distribution for its many effects I minus one has to sum to one and I have
减一必须加和为一，而我有XI减1的三个值，所以K
minus one has to sum to one and I have three values of X I minus 1 so the K
three values of X I minus 1 so the K squared minus K okay for a Markov chain
减去负K的平方对于一个马尔可夫链基本上可以看到，成本是线性的
squared minus K okay for a Markov chain basically you can see the cost is linear
basically you can see the cost is linear in M you can see here K 2 parallel
在M中，您可以在这里看到K 2并行，这不是很好
in M you can see here K 2 parallel alright that's not very good
alright that's not very good so this is sort of the most trivial case
所以这是最简单的情况，而图表基本上是针对该情况
so this is sort of the most trivial case and and the graph basically for that
and and the graph basically for that looks like now I know some of you have I
看起来现在我知道你们中的一些人我是说我假设要服用其他
looks like now I know some of you have I mean I'm assuming of taking other
mean I'm assuming of taking other statistics process some took the course
统计过程有的上了学期的课程，有的没有上过学的课程。
statistics process some took the course the semester and some have not
the semester and some have not so you know I know you got some homework
所以你知道我知道你有一些作业问题，假设是
so you know I know you got some homework problems where the assumption was that
problems where the assumption was that you look at the graph and you know
您看一下图表，就知道天空中的一切意味着什么
you look at the graph and you know everything from the skies what it means
everything from the skies what it means with I suggest this if when you come
我建议您在遇到这些问题时不知道
with I suggest this if when you come across these things and you don't know
across these things and you don't know or you want to see more references send
或者您想查看更多参考，请给我发送电子邮件，我将给您发送的邮件很少
or you want to see more references send me an email I will send you very few
me an email I will send you very few pages of reading to see these things in
阅读页面以详细了解这些内容，以防万一您没有看到
pages of reading to see these things in in detail just in case you haven't seen
in detail just in case you haven't seen them before
他们之前，所以这是
them before so this is
so this is the cases with discreet Barnabas and I
谨慎的Barnabas案，我举几个例子，让我们来看一下
the cases with discreet Barnabas and I give you a few examples so let's look at
give you a few examples so let's look at the example of the top okay it says we
最上面的例子很好，它说我们现在把一切都离散了
the example of the top okay it says we take everything to be discrete right now
take everything to be discrete right now okay so I have a Markov chain
好的，所以我旁边有一个马尔可夫链，考试旁边，但是x1
okay so I have a Markov chain okay next one next to the exam but x1
okay next one next to the exam but x1 depends on I mean you can sit here some
取决于我的意思是您可以坐在这里，有些参数意味着您对您不满意
depends on I mean you can sit here some parameters mean you are excused from you
parameters mean you are excused from you to examine some um and mainly depends
检查一些，主要取决于手段的一般组成或
to examine some um and mainly depends means the general the composition or
means the general the composition or factorization of the distribution of
分布的因式分解，我们在看这张图
factorization of the distribution of we're looking at this graph the
we're looking at this graph the distribution is given you on its power
分配给定了它的力量就给定x1分配给x2
distribution is given you on its power alright the distributions of x2 given x1
alright the distributions of x2 given x1 and given you two extremes even
给了你两个极端，甚至给了你三个接受
and given you two extremes even explained given in you three acceptance
explained given in you three acceptance of this product okay
该产品的价格还可以潜在我的P的产品
of this product okay potential the product of P of me to feel
potential the product of P of me to feel from you three P of MU M so this is the
从您的MU M的三个P中得到，所以这是对间隙的因式分解，好吧，嗯
from you three P of MU M so this is the factorization over the gap okay so um
factorization over the gap okay so um are basically the parameters that are
基本上是定义此动力学模型所需的参数，或者
are basically the parameters that are needed to define this dynamical model or
needed to define this dynamical model or the terms you have to go from X minus n
您必须将X减n减1改为xn的条件，在这种情况下，您
the terms you have to go from X minus n minus 1 to xn okay and in this case you
minus 1 to xn okay and in this case you know there's no levels because they are
知道没有水平，因为它们是离散的并且取K值
know there's no levels because they are discrete and take K values
discrete and take K values this can take K values and I will need
这可以取K值，我需要优先考虑一些好的贫困
this can take K values and I will need to put some priority good poverty put is
to put some priority good poverty put is a dealer distribution the red
经销商分布红色分布将非常重要
a dealer distribution the red distributions are going to count very
distributions are going to count very often later in the question I only want
通常在问题的后面，我只希望您浏览Wikipedia并获得一些
often later in the question I only want you to look on Wikipedia and get some
you to look on Wikipedia and get some sense of what
基本上是先于共轭的意义
sense of what it's a conjugate prior basically to the
it's a conjugate prior basically to the Volta and Moody distribution so it's
Volta和Moody的分布，因此演奏非常重要，
Volta and Moody distribution so it's very important to to play and it's
very important to to play and it's social a very sort of interesting topic
社会是一个非常有趣的研究主题，因为在这里我非常
social a very sort of interesting topic for research because here some I very
for research because here some I very recent ideas a colleague from dear
最近的想法来自亲爱的克莱尔（Claire）的同事处理不发行
recent ideas a colleague from dear Claire processes not distributions okay
Claire processes not distributions okay and statistical computer science because
和统计计算机科学，因为这是一个非常重要的主题
and statistical computer science because this is a very important topic does this
this is a very important topic does this looking at this graph does it make any
看看这张图，这对优化没有任何意义吗？
looking at this graph does it make any sense right the optimization this is all
sense right the optimization this is all my own on battabox my exes and my new is
我自己在battabox上的exe文件和我的新文件都没什么，所以我什么都不做，所以
my own on battabox my exes and my new is nothing I don't give anything right so
nothing I don't give anything right so the Joint Distribution I write it like
联合发行我这样写
the Joint Distribution I write it like that
that is this equation like the first and
这个方程式像第一和第二行一样吗？
is this equation like the first and second line do we make tent no general
对，所以你知道你必须把这些条件交给父母
right so you you know you have to put these conditionals giving the parents
these conditionals giving the parents but then sometimes when her parents
但是有时候当她的父母同时没有父母时，他会来
but then sometimes when her parents meanwhile has no parent so he will come
meanwhile has no parent so he will come home Nia took has no plans we come alone
尼亚（Nia）带回家没有任何计划，我们一个人来吧，他不是父亲，他一个人来。
home Nia took has no plans we come alone um he's no father he come alone all
um he's no father he come alone all right and because we would be interested
是的，因为我们最终会对贝叶斯感兴趣
right and because we would be interested to eventually sort of the Bayesian
to eventually sort of the Bayesian analysis on the parameters in the model
对模型中的参数进行分析可以很好地处理先验问题
analysis on the parameters in the model is good to put the prior all right a lot
is good to put the prior all right a lot prior theories to declare prior that is
先验理论要声明的先验将具有自己的参数类型
prior theories to declare prior that is going to have its own type of parameters
going to have its own type of parameters alpha alpha mutant yep
alpha alpha突变是
从n等于2谢谢是的，所以乘积等于2我希望我
going to have its own type of parameters alpha alpha mutant yep
from n equal to 2 thank you yep okay so the product to be m equal to 2 I wish I
从n等于2谢谢是的，所以乘积等于2我希望我
the product to be m equal to 2 I wish I can just say to my computer please
可以只对我的电脑说，请更改不是，我不知道为什么
can just say to my computer please change doesn't I don't know why the
change doesn't I don't know why the technology is not as sophisticated so
技术不是那么复杂，所以如果我忘记更改，请提醒我
technology is not as sophisticated so please remind me if I forget to change
please remind me if I forget to change this and the same I supposed to have to
这和我本来应该正确的一样，所以这就是
this and the same I supposed to have to it right okay so this is the very
it right okay so this is the very general setting and I am taking the same
常规设置，我遇到了相同的问题，实际上是在简化它
general setting and I am taking the same problem and I'm actually simplifying it
problem and I'm actually simplifying it enormously with a second Republic the
第二个共和国极大地提高了图形模型的效率，这是什么
enormously with a second Republic the graphical model so what's the
graphical model so what's the simplification that you see on the
您在第二张图上看到的简化是巨大的，那是什么
simplification that you see on the second graph that is enormous so what is
second graph that is enormous so what is the simplification you can stick on the
您可以坚持在顶部的简化，以便参数开始我做了一些
the simplification you can stick on the top so the parameters start I made some
top so the parameters start I made some using the same parameters to define all
使用相同的参数来定义所有这种条件概率
using the same parameters to define all this conditional probability
this conditional probability distributions okay I mean that's of
分布好，我的意思是这当然是一个主要假设，但您可以
distributions okay I mean that's of course a major assumption but you can
course a major assumption but you can appreciate the inference with one meal
欣赏一顿饭的推论而不是与成千上万次的推论
appreciate the inference with one meal versus doing influence with thousands of
versus doing influence with thousands of gnu's
gnu没事，所以参数的时间
gnu's okay all right so time of the parameters
okay all right so time of the parameters makes things extremely late so I think
使事情变得非常晚，所以我认为也许在处理过程中
makes things extremely late so I think maybe in the processing we maybe
maybe in the processing we maybe advocated this problem and we said is
提倡这个问题，我们说在这个问题上不会经常出现
advocated this problem and we said is not going to be here so often in this
not going to be here so often in this course but let me use this as a sort of
当然，但让我用它作为反例，所以假设我们有M
course but let me use this as a sort of a counter example so let's say we have M
a counter example so let's say we have M variables again that they are discrete
变量又是离散的，每个变量可以取K个不同的值
variables again that they are discrete and each of them can take K different
and each of them can take K different states and I'm interested in some sort
州，我对某种分类问题很感兴趣
states and I'm interested in some sort of a classification problem strike one
of a classification problem strike one for example to know if X 1 to X what's
例如，要知道X 1到X是否y等于1的概率为右
for example to know if X 1 to X what's the probability of y equal to 1 right
the probability of y equal to 1 right given X 1 and X n so maybe why can't one
给定X 1和X n，所以为什么一个不能是1000
given X 1 and X n so maybe why can't one is 1000 from
is 1000 from later come y equal to zero some other
后来，y等于零，其他高斯也可以，但是我有兴趣
later come y equal to zero some other Gaussian okay but I'm interested to just
Gaussian okay but I'm interested to just compute only to do classification in
仅以这种可能性进行计算以进行分类
compute only to do classification in this probability
this probability okay so somebody can build this
好的，所以有人可以构建我们之前拥有的复杂图形
okay so somebody can build this complicated graphs that we had before
complicated graphs that we had before and form the joint probability of Y and
并形成Y和所有XS的联合概率，并且对
and form the joint probability of Y and all the XS alright and do interested of
all the XS alright and do interested of graph but an approach that is actually
图，但是如果您唯一携带的是
graph but an approach that is actually the best if the only thing you carry is
the best if the only thing you carry is this conditional probability is actually
这个条件概率实际上是试图以某种非线性来翻转它
this conditional probability is actually to try to flip it in some non-linearity
to try to flip it in some non-linearity and what non-linearity here is the
Sigmoid函数在这里是什么非线性，所以基本上
and what non-linearity here is the sigmoid function so basically what you
sigmoid function so basically what you say is you know what I'm going to model
说您知道我要将此模型建模为S型函数吗
say is you know what I'm going to model this as a sigmoid function where I'm
this as a sigmoid function where I'm gonna use some linear approach linear
将使用一些线性方法对艺术家进行线性插值
gonna use some linear approach linear interpolation of the artists okay with
interpolation of the artists okay with some unknown parameters W so you know
一些未知的参数W，所以您知道条件分布或其他任何东西
some unknown parameters W so you know conditional distributions or anything
conditional distributions or anything like that and then of analysis or the
像这样，然后进行分析，或者是W，而我只有M加小W
like that and then of analysis or the W's and I only have M plus small W all
W's and I only have M plus small W all right so this says things you can write
对，这表示您可以按分类数量编写内容
right so this says things you can write in the quantities of classification
in the quantities of classification these are the best ways to actually to
这些是使用参数实际对此建模的最佳方法是
these are the best ways to actually to model this using a parameter is
model this using a parameter is basically model for this conditional
基本上围绕这种条件分布建立模型
basically model for this conditional distribution around about claiming the
distribution around about claiming the whole Joint Distribution working sort of
整个联合发行工作都在叙述的意义上，但是
whole Joint Distribution working sort of in in in of the narrative sense okay but
in in in of the narrative sense okay but this gives you only this probability you
这只会给您这种可能性，您只能做些事而不能做很多事
this gives you only this probability you cannot do much except just using that
cannot do much except just using that probability that's good you stop there
好的可能性，如果不好的话就停在那儿，那就要看一下
probability that's good you stop there if it's not good then it has to look at
if it's not good then it has to look at a more general way
更一般的方式
好吧，告诉我一个例子，你们应该在家庭作业中
if it's not good then it has to look at a more general way
all right tell me the example that you guys should be given in the homework
好吧，告诉我一个例子，你们应该在家庭作业中
guys should be given in the homework okay anybody has go to this problem so
好的，有人解决了这个问题，所以让我为您解决这个问题，因为我还没有
okay anybody has go to this problem so let me work it for you because I haven't
let me work it for you because I haven't read the solution so I don't know what
阅读解决方案，所以我不知道它在问什么，也许他在问你要做
read the solution so I don't know what it is asking maybe he's asking you to do
it is asking maybe he's asking you to do what's on the slide and flop is the case
幻灯片和翻牌上的内容是您最好纠正我的幻灯片的情况，因为我
what's on the slide and flop is the case you better correct my slide because I'm
you better correct my slide because I'm sure something must be wrong
确保某些东西一定是错误的，好吧，不仅键入错误，而且您
sure something must be wrong all right not just typed wrong but you
all right not just typed wrong but you know so you guys find a mistake software
知道，所以你们发现了错误的软件线性化模型，您可以再三考虑
know so you guys find a mistake software linearization model you can think again
linearization model you can think again of you know where this conditional
你们中的人知道X i的这种有条件分布给它的父母在哪里
of you know where this conditional distributions of X i given its parents
distributions of X i given its parents we're going to model it as a linear
我们将其建模为线性千位数模型，这意味着什么
we're going to model it as a linear thousand model what does that mean means
thousand model what does that mean means we're going to take the mean of this
我们将采用此条件的均值作为加权值
we're going to take the mean of this condition the tribution to be a weighted
condition the tribution to be a weighted average of their parents this is what
他们父母的平均值，这就是这个加上一些偏见，然后
average of their parents this is what this is plus some bias term and then
this is plus some bias term and then plus some noise this is very generic
加上一些噪声，这是非常通用的，实际上这就是我们所说的线性
plus some noise this is very generic actually this is what we call the linear
actually this is what we call the linear Gaussian model alright so in this case
高斯模型好了，在这种情况下，这个线性模型有什么特别之处
Gaussian model alright so in this case what is very particular for this linear
what is very particular for this linear Gaussian model is that the axis that you
高斯模型是用于定义均值的轴
Gaussian model is that the axis that you use to define the mean defined from the
use to define the mean defined from the products right this one of the finest
这款X J最好的产品之一就是日记本的父母
products right this one of the finest this X J's are the parents of no diary
this X J's are the parents of no diary but this mean is linear in X J and then
但这在XJ中是线性的，然后我插入了一些噪声V
but this mean is linear in X J and then I plug in some noise V so the announced
I plug in some noise V so the announced basically in the problem our world is
基本上在这个问题上我们的世界是双重使用的偏见条款
basically in the problem our world is double used all right the bias terms
double used all right the bias terms based and the variance is V okay so if
基于，并且方差为V，所以如果您要共享此模型
based and the variance is V okay so if you want to share this being a model
you want to share this being a model written sort of in an algebraic form you
可以用代数形式写成VEX嗨
written sort of in an algebraic form you can say the VEX hi
can say the VEX hi the main value plus square root of VI
从正常高斯算起的VI的主值加上平方根，但它们
the main value plus square root of VI times from normal Gaussian but they
times from normal Gaussian but they actually okay with this elementary
实际上可以使用此基本属性，因此您可以通过这种方式看到
actually okay with this elementary properties so you can see this this way
properties so you can see this this way or you can see it this way it is the
或者你可以这样看，是一样的事情
or you can see it this way it is the same thing okay
same thing okay so linear motion because you know this
线性运动，因为您知道这是平均值的线性函数
so linear motion because you know this the in the mean is a linear function of
the in the mean is a linear function of the exist the linearity comes everywhere
线性到处都是高斯，因为不仅如此
the exist the linearity comes everywhere it's Gaussian because not only this
it's Gaussian because not only this condition distribution of X i given the
给定父级的X i的条件分布是向下壳，因此您可以
condition distribution of X i given the parent is down shell for that so you can
parent is down shell for that so you can so if you take all of these gardens you
因此，如果您将所有这些花园都带走，则可以将它们彼此相乘
so if you take all of these gardens you multiply them with each other if you
multiply them with each other if you expand and then you close the square as
扩大，然后关闭正方形，因为他们说您可以解决
expand and then you close the square as they say you can solve that the joint
they say you can solve that the joint distribution is also Gaussian right it's
分布也是高斯对，这是二次方，我又不是
distribution is also Gaussian right it's a quadratic I mean and I again I am NOT
a quadratic I mean and I again I am NOT doing the algebra because it's not water
进行代数运算是因为它不是水，但是如果您正确地使用原木并且您
doing the algebra because it's not water but if you take the logs right and you
but if you take the logs right and you come up the product of all these
得出所有这些分布的乘积成为
come up the product of all these distributions becomes summation of the
distributions becomes summation of the logs and then you get this squares and
日志，然后得到这个正方形，如果扩大它们，基本上可以得到
logs and then you get this squares and if you expand them you can basically get
if you expand them you can basically get a square for to fit that they're
一个适合他们是多元高斯的平方，所以这导致
a square for to fit that they're multivariate gaussian so this leads to
multivariate gaussian so this leads to the multivariate Gaussian so the problem
多元高斯，所以这里的问题是我们想要这个图，但是
the multivariate Gaussian so the problem here is we want for this graph but is
here is we want for this graph but is represented by this conditional
由这个条件分布表示的我们想要计算
represented by this conditional distributions we want to compute the
distributions we want to compute the mean of all the nodes and we want to
所有节点的均值，我们要计算协方差权，
mean of all the nodes and we want to compute the the covariance right and
这是他要您为我证明它们的方程式，这是我的方程式
this are the equations where he wants you to prove them for me they are my
you to prove them for me they are my sites but once you take some time to
站点，但是一旦您花费一些时间来证明此等式，因为它们是
sites but once you take some time to prove this equations because they are
prove this equations because they are not obvious okay nothing is obvious in
不太明显好吧，生活中什么都不明显，所以如果你刻薄，让我们
not obvious okay nothing is obvious in life and so if you take the mean let's
life and so if you take the mean let's here this is the main of the condition
在这里，这是下一个事件用语传统的主要条件
here this is the main of the condition of the tradition of next events parlance
of the tradition of next events parlance okay
好[鼓掌]
okay [Applause]
[Applause] take the main effect I is actually let
发挥主要作用我实际上是让我给这个方程式XI的含义
take the main effect I is actually let me give this equation the meaning of X I
me give this equation the meaning of X I is summation over the parents of Waj the
是对Waj的父母的求和，A和bi的均值和
is summation over the parents of Waj the mean effect A plus bi and the mean of
mean effect A plus bi and the mean of this which is zero all right
这是零好
使用这个小方程式，这意味着如果您将它们放在一起
mean effect A plus bi and the mean of this which is zero all right
using this little equation the this means if you put them together alright
使用这个小方程式，这意味着如果您将它们放在一起
means if you put them together alright if you calculate them recursively and
如果您递归地计算它们，然后按顺序排列它们，您将知道
if you calculate them recursively and you put them in order you know it will
you put them in order you know it will give you the mean of the multivariate
给你多元体的平均值将退出每个人都说这
give you the mean of the multivariate body will exit everybody says this the
body will exit everybody says this the question I'm just using this and I take
问题，我只是用这个，我取XI的平均值，在那里求和
question I'm just using this and I take the mean of X I the summation there will
the mean of X I the summation there will be the mean of its J this is constant
是它的J的均值，这是常数，这是零，所以
be the mean of its J this is constant the mean of this is zero alright so
the mean of this is zero alright so basically they have very testy relation
基本上他们之间有很强的亲密关系
basically they have very testy relation and those means of what I put them
and those means of what I put them together in a vector form will give me
向量形式的平均值会给我向量X的均值
together in a vector form will give me the mean of vector X
the mean of vector X okay now bit more complicated the name
好吧，现在稍微复杂一点，协方差的名称给出了一个
okay now bit more complicated the name of the covariance is giving sort of a
of the covariance is giving sort of a similar expression this coefficient WJ k
类似的表达式，这个系数WJ k对于父母的k我必须用一块蛋糕
similar expression this coefficient WJ k for k of the parent i have to use a cake
for k of the parent i have to use a cake here because there's an ion is a there
在这里，因为那里有一个离子，所以WJ k激发的协方差
here because there's an ion is a there right so WJ k the covariance of excite
right so WJ k the covariance of excite with the XK minus of X I XJ so notice
XX减去XI XJ，所以请注意这里是城市衰落的aj
with the XK minus of X I XJ so notice here there's a j from the urban decay
here there's a j from the urban decay that are the parlance of j and then
是j的说法，然后有一个额外的对，就是另一个
that are the parlance of j and then there is an extra pair that is another
there is an extra pair that is another function alright so a equal to RF i and
函数正常，所以等于RF i和j等于，否则0的平方根
function alright so a equal to RF i and j is equal otherwise 0 square root of
j is equal otherwise 0 square root of the IV j mr. variance is right so i need
IV先生方差是正确的，所以我需要VI VIJ，当我喜欢
the IV j mr. variance is right so i need to have VI VJ and when i like the
to have VI VJ and when i like the situation I forgot to maybe to put this
这种情况我忘了也许将它放在上一张幻灯片中，这是给我的
situation I forgot to maybe to put this from the previous slide this is for I
from the previous slide this is for I less or equal to J so you may want to
小于或等于J，因此您可能想取和
less or equal to J so you may want to take and
take and so this in the weight of a habit is for
所以这个习惯对我来说等于或小于果冻，如果你
so this in the weight of a habit is for I less or equal to jelly okay if you
I less or equal to jelly okay if you know this right you can need something
知道这项权利，您可能需要其他可以使用对称性的东西，并且您可以
know this right you can need something else you can use symmetry and you can
else you can use symmetry and you can get for I greater than say a similar
为了我，我比说一个类似的表情要大，但这少了合唱团，或者
get for I greater than say a similar expression but this is choir less or
expression but this is choir less or equal to Z how do you prove this
等于Z您如何证明这个方程式不问您这个问题？
equal to Z how do you prove this equation alright doesn't ask you this or
equation alright doesn't ask you this or I don't know if he does anything they
我不知道他是否做过任何事，他们说可以证明一切正常，所以如果您
I don't know if he does anything they say prove it okay all right so if you
say prove it okay all right so if you want to prove it so if you want the
想证明这一点，如果您想通过定义来定义XI XJ的协方差为
want to prove it so if you want the covariance of X I XJ by definition is
covariance of X I XJ by definition is this
这就像XY减去X的平均值
this it's like if XY minus the mean of X
it's like if XY minus the mean of X sorry XJ minus the mean of XJ I'm using
对不起，XJ减去XJ的平均值，我在用这个，你可以离开这个关系
sorry XJ minus the mean of XJ I'm using this you can leave this relation this
this you can leave this relation this linear starting point that I had the urn
我有骨灰盒的线性起始点，我要减去XI的均值，
linear starting point that I had the urn and I'm subtracting the means of X I and
and I'm subtracting the means of X I and XJ and basically I stopped invest and he
XJ和我基本上停止了投资，而他会在今年秋天采取这种情况
XJ and basically I stopped invest and he will take this fall will case amount of
will take this fall will case amount of jail ok so now I'm going to have a
监狱好吧，现在我将对j WJ k和
jail ok so now I'm going to have a summation of the points of j WJ k and
summation of the points of j WJ k and then i'm going to have the expectation
那么我将对这个括号有个期望，最后想到的是
then i'm going to have the expectation of this parentheses final thought is the
of this parentheses final thought is the covariance of X I X K so the first times
XIXK的协方差，所以第一次出现
covariance of X I X K so the first times that is it there and then there is the
that is it there and then there is the expectation of this parentheses times
如果她会说，括号的期望乘以这个术语所涉及的时间
expectation of this parentheses times this term that involves if she'll say
this term that involves if she'll say all right and if the previous equation
好的，如果前面的方程式平方但期望的进度需要
all right and if the previous equation square but progress of expectation needs
square but progress of expectation needs to come to be equal to rest and the only
变得等于休息，这是我真正能够实现的唯一方式
to come to be equal to rest and the only way that I have been able to actually
way that I have been able to actually prove this is sort of doing it
证明这是一种递归的方式，所以如果你们来
prove this is sort of doing it recursively okay so if you guys come up
recursively okay so if you guys come up with a cleaner way not only you send me
用一种更清洁的方式，不仅您给了我正确的证明，而且还向我发送了
with a cleaner way not only you send me the right proof but you send me the
the right proof but you send me the correct
正确的问题，以剪切和粘贴我的风格
correct question to cut and paste on my style
question to cut and paste on my style it's today because I saw to play not
这是今天，因为我看到自己对教务长并不特别满意
it's today because I saw to play not particularly happy with provost
particularly happy with provost derivation but so again we want to pull
推导，所以我们又想拉这个x naught的期望是
derivation but so again we want to pull the expectation of this x naught is
the expectation of this x naught is equal to that and the way that I do it
等于那个，而我做的方式是我写了我们原著的其余部分
equal to that and the way that I do it is I write rest from our original
is I write rest from our original equation right I stops you this in terms
方程式对，我就其功能和价值阻止了您，对，这是
equation right I stops you this in terms of its power and values right this is
of its power and values right this is the expectation okay and then whether
期望还好，然后我是否开始做就记得我
the expectation okay and then whether whether I started doing is remember I
whether I started doing is remember I have a no-life here
这里没有生命，文件具有默认节点I，并且
have a no-life here the files have default node I and the
the files have default node I and the parents of higher default that so what I
高违约率的父母，所以我对此进行递归介绍
parents of higher default that so what I this I recursively introduce the
this I recursively introduce the parlance of Pi and then for its power in
Pi的说法，然后根据其在PI MI中的功能介绍自己的术语，而我
parlance of Pi and then for its power in the PI M I introduce its own term and I
the PI M I introduce its own term and I keep doing this until it's norm so when
继续这样做直到它成为常态，这样当您这样做时就可以了
keep doing this until it's norm so when you do it sort of this way okay it comes
you do it sort of this way okay it comes up but when you take it
上升，但是当您最常使用它时，并期望
up but when you take it most times that and expectations the
most times that and expectations the contributions you will get from this
您将从此求和中得到的贡献留给您知道为零，
contributions you will get from this summation left to you know to zero and
summation left to you know to zero and then you're going to care basically this
那么您将基本上要关心这个BJP I epsilon R epsilon J的期望
then you're going to care basically this BJP I epsilon R epsilon J expectation
BJP I epsilon R epsilon J expectation which effectively at the end of the day
在一天结束时有效地为您提供了这一点
which effectively at the end of the day will give you this
will give you this I'm highlighting the proof is part of
我要强调的是，如果您想看一下证明，它是您家庭作业的一部分
I'm highlighting the proof is part of your homework if you want to look at it
your homework if you want to look at it okay it sounds about right
好吧，听起来不错，但这将用于计算
okay it sounds about right but this is going to compute
but this is going to compute expectations this is how you complete
期望这就是您完成两个方程式的协方差的方式
expectations this is how you complete the covariance both equations are
the covariance both equations are requested because to compute the
要求，因为要计算X IJ的协方差小于或小于
requested because to compute the covariance of X IJ with high in less or
covariance of X IJ with high in less or equal to J you need the prevalence of
等于J，您需要与J的父代一起兴奋的流行，并且
equal to J you need the prevalence of excited with a parent of J and to
excited with a parent of J and to compute this you need the parents of K
计算这个，你需要K等的父母，等等，这是
compute this you need the parents of K and etc etc from here it's the the
and etc etc from here it's the the let me give you an example if you have
让我给你举个例子，如果你有三分钟的话
let me give you an example if you have three minutes
对第一印象的期望，您能告诉我的第一印象
the first impression the expectation can you tell me for first equation control
好吧，我提醒你，我提醒你，这个很好的方程式是对任何事物的期望
alright I remind you I remind you this nice equation the expectation of any
nice equation the expectation of any node is w IJ times the expectation of
节点是IJ乘以12 J飞行员的期望值，好吧，我告诉
node is w IJ times the expectation of the pilots of 12 J okay I'll tell the
the pilots of 12 J okay I'll tell the parents pi times D I so okay not great I
父母pi次DI所以还可以，我不好
希望他们有百日草的记忆来记住这个方程式，而不是三个
the pilots of 12 J okay I'll tell the parents pi times D I so okay not great I
want them to be with zinnias memory to remember this equation right not three
希望他们有百日草的记忆来记住这个方程式，而不是三个
remember this equation right not three what are the odds of not playing just
不玩游戏的几率是多少
x的期望是北欧人期望的两倍
remember this equation right not three what are the odds of not playing just
the expectation of x two times the expectation of Nordics few and what is
x的期望是北欧人期望的两倍
expectation of Nordics few and what is the expectation of no to the expectation
否对注a的期望为1倍于
the expectation of no to the expectation of note a will be 1 times the
of note a will be 1 times the expectation of X 1 and what is the
X 1的期望值和X 1的期望值是B 1，因为那里
expectation of X 1 and what is the expectation of X 1 is B 1 because there
expectation of X 1 is B 1 because there are no power
没有权力，所以当你把所有这一切
are no power all right so when you put all of this
all right so when you put all of this together you get this nice integration
在一起，您将获得本，本以及类似的良好集成
together you get this nice integration of this and this and similarly good
of this and this and similarly good check for example let's say the
例如，假设X 1和X 3的协方差为
check for example let's say the covariance of X 1 and X 3 I have the
covariance of X 1 and X 3 I have the formula clear so we don't have to go
公式很明确，所以我们不必来回回荡，这就是公式
formula clear so we don't have to go back and forth this is the formula that
back and forth this is the formula that says they are the parents of of 3 the
说他们是3的父母，3仍然直的部分会做3
says they are the parents of of 3 the parts of 3 still straight will be done 3
parts of 3 still straight will be done 3 2 times the covariance of X 1 and X 2
X 1和X 2的协方差的2倍X 1和X 2的协方差是
2 times the covariance of X 1 and X 2 the covariance of X 1 and X 2 unique the
the covariance of X 1 and X 2 unique the potential 2 which is 1 so it will be W 2
势2等于1，所以它将是W 2 1乘以X 1 X 1的协方差
potential 2 which is 1 so it will be W 2 1 times the covariance of X 1 X 1 plus
1 times the covariance of X 1 X 1 plus these delta function 1 2 times B 2 this
这些增量函数1 2乘以B 2该函数为0，所以得到W 3 2 W 2 1和
these delta function 1 2 times B 2 this function is 0 so you get W 3 2 W 2 1 and
function is 0 so you get W 3 2 W 2 1 and the covariance of X 1 X 1 is V 1 ok so
X 1 X 1的协方差是V 1 ok，所以这是一个复杂而痛苦的计算
the covariance of X 1 X 1 is V 1 ok so it's a complicated painful calculation
it's a complicated painful calculation we have on the other hand it's a closed
另一方面，这是一个封闭形式的解决方案，您的意思是
we have on the other hand it's a closed form solution you have the mean just by
form solution you have the mean just by playing together with this conditional
与此条件概率分布一起玩，您可以
playing together with this conditional probability distributions you can
probability distributions you can compute the mean of the Joint
计算联合分布和协方差的均值，以及
compute the mean of the Joint Distribution and the covariance and and
Distribution and the covariance and and and you know you have everything alright
你知道你一切都好
这个模型有多少个参数，所以模型中的参数又是
Distribution and the covariance and and and you know you have everything alright
how many parameters from this model so again the parameters in the model are
这个模型有多少个参数，所以模型中的参数又是
again the parameters in the model are these variances and there are diverse
这些差异，并且存在多种多样，因为您知道我想我的上帝
these variances and there are diverse because you know I suppose my god just
because you know I suppose my god just denote in this case alright so I have
在这种情况下表示正确，所以我有它的变体，然后它说
denote in this case alright so I have the variant it and then it says the
the variant it and then it says the parameters W IJ Rd square minus V over 2
参数W IJ Rd平方减去V大于2如果您还记得这一点，我该怎么办
parameters W IJ Rd square minus V over 2 what do I get out if you remember this
what do I get out if you remember this problem is defined the you know your
问题定义了，你知道你对父母的依赖，所以如果
problem is defined the you know your dependence on the parents right so if
dependence on the parents right so if I'm interested to try on w12 how much is
我有兴趣尝试w12，w12多少是不是我们想要0正确
I'm interested to try on w12 how much is w12 there's not that we want to 0 right
w12 there's not that we want to 0 right I mean the only thing I have here is
我的意思是，我唯一看到的就是让我看3号，我有W 3 2并且
I mean the only thing I have here is let's if I look at no.3 I have W 3 2 and
let's if I look at no.3 I have W 3 2 and W you know W 3 2 is nonzero because the
W知道W 3 2是非零的，因为2的父代是所有三个的父代
W you know W 3 2 is nonzero because the parent of 2 is the parent of three all
parent of 2 is the parent of three all right so I am looking is this not B to
正确，所以我正在寻找这不是B是一个较低的三角矩阵和一个较低的
right so I am looking is this not B to be a lower triangular matrix and a lower
be a lower triangular matrix and a lower triangular matrix change the dimensions
三角矩阵的变化尺寸是平方减去B的总和
triangular matrix change the dimensions is what totally the square minus B in
is what totally the square minus B in the Bellarmine I'll then take half you
贝拉明我要拿一半，你得到这个平方减去B等于2
the Bellarmine I'll then take half you get this square minus B over 2
如果解决了这个2就是3这个复杂的线性高斯模型
it comes that this complicated linear Gaussian model if you solve this 2 is 3
Gaussian model if you solve this 2 is 3 times 3 plus 1 over 2 which is actually
3乘1加2，实际上与您的协方差矩阵相同
times 3 plus 1 over 2 which is actually the same as the covariance matrix of you
the same as the covariance matrix of you know the division alright symmetric
知道除法对称各种指标，以便有效地
know the division alright symmetric various metrics so that effectively the
various metrics so that effectively the Joint Distribution is a Gaussian alright
联合分配是高斯的，所以显然这可能需要
Joint Distribution is a Gaussian alright so obviously this probably needs to be
so obviously this probably needs to be sort of equivalent to to you know to
相当于您所知道的此顺序所需的参数顺序
sort of equivalent to to you know to this order of parameters required for a
this order of parameters required for a multivariate Gaussian basically to
多元高斯基本定义协方差矩阵好简单
multivariate Gaussian basically to define the covariance matrix okay simple
define the covariance matrix okay simple 12 approach to this problem that is from
解决此问题的12种方法，来自马尔萨斯书，这是一个非常重要的中心
12 approach to this problem that is from Malthus book and it is Center for a very
Malthus book and it is Center for a very simple calculation without any recursive
简单的计算，没有任何递归关系，所以您可能会感激
simple calculation without any recursive relationships okay so you may appreciate
relationships okay so you may appreciate this derivation because only one slide
这种推导是因为只有一张或两张幻灯片
this derivation because only one slide or two
所以我从元数据中保留了表示法，所以不要混淆那是多少个方程式
so I kept the notation from a meta so don't mixed up that's how many equations
don't mixed up that's how many equations but this kilonewtons acting on the same
但是这个千牛顿在相同的问题上起作用，所以在几个V中
but this kilonewtons acting on the same problem alright so in several V this
problem alright so in several V this conditional variance here he is using
条件方差，这里他使用的是Sigma T Square，这是我的偏见
conditional variance here he is using Sigma T Square this is my bias term was
Sigma T Square this is my bias term was because ultimately the same problem okay
因为最终会出现同样的问题，所以她所做的就是着色
because ultimately the same problem okay so what she does is the coloring have
so what she does is the coloring have bunnies I subtracted the mean from the
兔子，我从每个节点的值中减去了平均值
bunnies I subtracted the mean from the values of each node
values of each node okay so okay so from this node and the
好吧，好吧，所以从这个节点和父母基本上会做的不是
okay so okay so from this node and the parents basically would have done is not
parents basically would have done is not subtracting the mean okay and so this is
减去均值就可以了，所以这与我拥有的方程式相似
subtracting the mean okay and so this is the similar equation with what I had
the similar equation with what I had before this is like my noise level
之前就像我以前的噪音水平标准，但是通过写
before this is like my noise level emtional I had before but by writing the
emtional I had before but by writing the equation like not where the mean of the
等式不是正常值的平均值明确出现的地方，我可以
equation like not where the mean of the normal values come explicitly I can
normal values come explicitly I can write this whole equation as a vector
将整个方程式写成向量形式如下X减mu是向量
write this whole equation as a vector form as follows X minus mu is a vector
form as follows X minus mu is a vector equal lower diagonal matrix W similar to
等于下对角矩阵W，类似于我们之前乘以X减去Mew所得的值
equal lower diagonal matrix W similar to what we had before times X minus Mew
what we had before times X minus Mew okay and I can write this as the matrix
好的，我可以这样写，因为矩阵s在这种情况下将是
okay and I can write this as the matrix s in this case will be the banner that
s in this case will be the banner that contains the noise viruses okay I
包含噪音病毒，好吧，我想是的，在我们得到之前
contains the noise viruses okay I suppose yes this before we had the
suppose yes this before we had the square root of the variance so this is
方差的平方根，所以这就是标准偏差
square root of the variance so this is you know it's the standard deviation so
you know it's the standard deviation so this correct stress is the diagonal of
这个正确的应力是Sigma的对角线乘以向量Z，这就是
this correct stress is the diagonal of Sigma times the vector Z this is the
Sigma times the vector Z this is the same equation I had discovered the only
我发现的相同方程式现在唯一的区别是，我可以
same equation I had discovered the only difference is now alright that I can
difference is now alright that I can write this as a matrix equation where
将此写成矩阵方程式，它与表达式有什么不同
write this as a matrix equation where what is different from the expression we
what is different from the expression we used before is that instead of Texas
之前使用的是代替X减去得克萨斯州的得克萨斯州
used before is that instead of Texas with X minus left the means of the
with X minus left the means of the northern body and there's a reason to do
北方的身体，这样做是有原因的，因为这是一个方程式，如果
northern body and there's a reason to do this because so this is an equation if
this because so this is an equation if you trying just to start with it will be
如果RS是该对角线的对角线，那么您尝试开始的时间将是s次。
you trying just to start with it will be s times if RS is this diagonal of the
s times if RS is this diagonal of the standard deviations in the conditional
条件分布的标准偏差，所以这是减去
standard deviations in the conditional distribution so this is e x minus mu you
distribution so this is e x minus mu you can see from here times 9 minus 9 is
从这里可以看到9减9将会变得很好，所以
can see from here times 9 minus 9 is going to come to be e all right so
going to come to be e all right so finally this explicitly e equal I - down
最终，这明显等于我-一年下来
finally this explicitly e equal I - down the year
the year alright a nice invertible matrix times X
好吧，一个很好的可逆矩阵乘以X减去mu就可以解决X
alright a nice invertible matrix times X minus mu all right and I can solve for X
minus mu all right and I can solve for X minus mu by inverting this matrix I
减去这个矩阵，我就减去W乘以P，好吧，所以f为f
minus mu by inverting this matrix I minus W times P all right and ok is f
minus W times P all right and ok is f prime Z when I try let me call this
素数Z当我尝试让我称这个矩阵为好矩阵时，该矩阵为U
prime Z when I try let me call this matrix you alright well this matrix is U
matrix you alright well this matrix is U times s times Z all right when we need
当我们需要复杂的计算时，可以乘以s乘以Z
times s times Z all right when we need the complicated calculation the
the complicated calculation the constraints approach the same as the
约束与X减去mu X减去mu的协方差相同
constraints approach the same as the covariance of X minus mu X minus mu from
covariance of X minus mu X minus mu from this equation is again this is me way
这个等式再次是这是我现在投资者精打细算的方式
this equation is again this is me way the investor fineliners now the use of
the investor fineliners now the use of the waist right so the terms of real
腰部合适，所以实时测试的条件是
the waist right so the terms of real times test as you remember is the
times test as you remember is the diagonal of the conditional standard
条件标准差s的对角线乘以G为负矢量，
diagonal of the conditional standard deviation s times G is minus vector and
deviation s times G is minus vector and the covariance of U times s times D from
U乘以D乘以D乘以D的协方差
the covariance of U times s times D from classical identity from your probability
classical identity from your probability cost is us times the covariance of J
成本是我们乘以J的协方差乘以它的转置
cost is us times the covariance of J times the transpose of this as you
times the transpose of this as you Forest Service identity so you get us
森林服务的身份，这样您就可以为我们提供四种不同的运动，因此请定义
Forest Service identity so you get us four different sports so define the
four different sports so define the covariance of the join vector X which we
我们需要的连接向量X的协方差
covariance of the join vector X which we need this you need to complete you and
need this you need to complete you and use in terms of the weights and you need
根据重量使用，您需要一个噪音体世界的巢穴
use in terms of the weights and you need s a nest of the noise body world the
s a nest of the noise body world the noise standard deviations of the
条件分布的噪声标准偏差，所以现在
noise standard deviations of the conditional distributions so now the
conditional distributions so now the pension calculation solo very cash
养老金计算单身非常现金投资者消失了一个窍门，
pension calculation solo very cash investors disappeared with one trick and
investors disappeared with one trick and the trick is to work not through the
诀窍是不通过实验而是使用X减亩
the trick is to work not through the experiments but with the X minus mu
experiments but with the X minus mu value okay so say q1 we need to
值还可以，所以说q1，我们需要实现此线性高斯模型
value okay so say q1 we need to implement this linear Gaussian model
implement this linear Gaussian model this is photo to the busiest way you can
这是最繁忙的方式的照片，您基本上可以通过这种方式获得期望
this is photo to the busiest way you can get basically the expectations the way
get basically the expectations the way we did in the earlier slide expectations
我们在前面的幻灯片中所做的期望很容易做到，我真的很紧凑
we did in the earlier slide expectations are very easy to do I was really compact
are very easy to do I was really compact so for example at this trivial case when
因此，例如在这种琐碎的情况下，当您将数据x1收集到xn时，它们全都
so for example at this trivial case when you collect data x1 to xn and they all
you collect data x1 to xn and they all come up from some distribution of some
从一些未知参数theta的分布中得出一个很好的方法
come up from some distribution of some unknown parameter theta a good way to
unknown parameter theta a good way to represent this so here actually I should
代表这个，所以实际上我应该在这里记笔记正确，这里是X 2 X 3
represent this so here actually I should have notes right is X 2 here X 3
have notes right is X 2 here X 3 etcetera xn so a good way to represent
etcetera xn，所以以紧凑的方式表示化合物的一种好方法是
etcetera xn so a good way to represent compound in a compact fashion list is to
compound in a compact fashion list is to represent this with a presentation the
通过演示文稿来表示这一点，vs从XI的背面跟随您
represent this with a presentation the vs. follows you from the backside at X I
vs. follows you from the backside at X I and you indicate that you have n
表示您有n个X实例
and you indicate that you have n instances of X all right
instances of X all right you have any generalizations of X I and
您对XI有任何概括，所有这些实现都具有相同的含义
you have any generalizations of X I and all of these realizations have the same
all of these realizations have the same theta when they come from the same
当它们来自具有参数的相同分布时，theta
theta when they come from the same distribution that there's a parameter
distribution that there's a parameter theta so theta has to be outside the box
theta，所以theta必须在盒子外面，因为只有东西在里面
theta so theta has to be outside the box because only thing things inside the
because only thing things inside the battery repeat things outside the next
电池重复下一个以外的东西基本上是独立的，嗨，好吧
battery repeat things outside the next are basically independent of hi okay so
are basically independent of hi okay so this is basically equivalent to the
这基本上等同于您在此处看到的表示法
this is basically equivalent to the notation that you see here for simple
notation that you see here for simple problems you can do this for more
问题，您可以针对更复杂的问题执行此操作，这可能是糖果
problems you can do this for more complicated problems this may be candy
complicated problems this may be candy but you have to do it carefully because
但您必须谨慎操作，因为其中一些盒子和复杂的
but you have to do it carefully because some of these boxes and complicated
some of these boxes and complicated distributions may be nested and you can
发行版可能是嵌套的，您可能会弄错您所知道的
distributions may be nested and you can sort of come up with wrong with you know
sort of come up with wrong with you know the wrong conclusions because your
结论错误，因为您的分布由该图表示
the wrong conclusions because your distribution represented by this graph
distribution represented by this graph of this graph is not the same so in this
该图的位置不一样，因此在这种情况下，如果您对关节
of this graph is not the same so in this case if you interested in the Joint
case if you interested in the Joint Distribution of all the variables the
下次分配所有变量，然后有n个实例
Distribution of all the variables the next time and then you have n instances
next time and then you have n instances of the probability of X i given theta
X i给定theta的概率，我们在这里用这个乘积看到
of the probability of X i given theta which we see with this product here so
which we see with this product here so this is the joint distribution and it's
这是关节的分布，与关节的确相同
this is the joint distribution and it's really identical to the Joint
really identical to the Joint Distribution of Yashida okay so this
Yashida的分布还可以，所以这又是一种更紧凑的方式，
Distribution of Yashida okay so this again it's a more compact way and it's
again it's a more compact way and it's called the plate notation for
称为板符号，用于表示图形模型
called the plate notation for representing graphical models
好的
all right
因此，如果这种情况不能持续下去，那是由于采用方式未知而导致的。
so if this don't extend come from adoption that has some unknown the mean
adoption that has some unknown the mean and variance that same your standard
和方差相同的标准差Sigma这是板
and variance that same your standard deviation Sigma this is the plate
deviation Sigma this is the plate notation for representing some good data
用参数mu表示来自此高斯的一些好的数据的符号
notation for representing some good data from this Gaussian with parameters mu
from this Gaussian with parameters mu and Sigma all right so the Joint
和西格玛没事，所以联合分配是西格玛和
and Sigma all right so the Joint Distribution is for unity of Sigma and
Distribution is for unity of Sigma and then you have M installations of the
则您有M个安装，给定了mu和Sigma或x的概率为x
then you have M installations of the probability of x given mu and Sigma or
probability of x given mu and Sigma or additionally to parents so this is a
除了父母，所以这减少了我们对金额的干扰
additionally to parents so this is a reduction the amount disruption where we
reduction the amount disruption where we have one of this you know everything
拥有其中之一，您就知道一切都表明每个节点X都依赖
have one of this you know everything indicating that every node X depends
indicating that every node X depends from you know Sigma or you prefer this
从您知道Sigma或您更喜欢这种雾屏符号，所以让我
from you know Sigma or you prefer this mister screen notation okay so let me
mister screen notation okay so let me finish
完成我们又有五分钟的时间
finish we have exactly five minutes again for
we have exactly five minutes again for those who have not seen regression
那些还没有看过回归模型的人，我建议您看一下
those who have not seen regression models I will suggest that you look on
models I will suggest that you look on on my lecture in you know in the poll
在我的演讲中，您知道民意调查和完全相同的问题
on my lecture in you know in the poll and the exact same problem basically
and the exact same problem basically limitation I don't think we're going to
局限性我不认为我们会回到
limitation I don't think we're going to come back to the aggression problems in
come back to the aggression problems in this course but right now I just want to
本课程，但现在我只想为您提供的模块化演示
this course but right now I just want to give you a modular presentation of for
give you a modular presentation of for regression for base and regression to
回归基础和回归，看看它如何工作，今天我们是
regression for base and regression to see how it works like so today we are
see how it works like so today we are given some data and T are the positive
给定一些数据，T是正值，我们尝试除法
given some data and T are the positive values and we try to the division
values and we try to the division fitting in the sense that for some unix
在某种意义上说是合适的，对于某些Unix，我们希望能够预测值
fitting in the sense that for some unix we want to be able to predict the value
we want to be able to predict the value of T and also the uncertainty in T so we
的T以及T的不确定性，因此我们提出了积分函数
of T and also the uncertainty in T so we come up with integration function that
come up with integration function that this basically in this case a linear
这基本上是线性模型，所以WI x 6i至少
this basically in this case a linear model okay so WI x 6i okay and least
model okay so WI x 6i okay and least this coefficients table review we take
该系数表回顾我们将它们作为随机底数，因此它们将
this coefficients table review we take them as random bottom so they're gonna
them as random bottom so they're gonna put some flour on them all right and so
可以在上面放些面粉，所以tmw的巨大可能性是，您可以
put some flour on them all right and so the giant probability of tmw is you can
the giant probability of tmw is you can think of being our measurements of some
认为是我们对某些给定点X的测量，但在此等式中是
think of being our measurements of some given points X but in this equation is
given points X but in this equation is not strong but the Joint Distribution of
不是很强，但是他们观察到的联合分布是T和
not strong but the Joint Distribution of what they have observed which is T and
what they have observed which is T and of this on all kilometers lovely you is
在所有可爱的公里中，您是边界时间的先验
of this on all kilometers lovely you is the prior in boundary times the
the prior in boundary times the likelihood of each data point TN with
每个数据点TN具有已知参数的可能性，所以这就是
likelihood of each data point TN with known parameters so this is how the
known parameters so this is how the aggression more than reaching the
侵略不仅仅是达到标准的感觉，好吧，这是
aggression more than reaching the standard sense all right this are the
standard sense all right this are the observations T the parameters WL unknown
观察值T参数WL未知可以
observations T the parameters WL unknown all right
all right so for every given X but the graph
所以对于每个给定的X，但图形不是很多，我强调这一点，我
so for every given X but the graph wasn't so much and I emphasize this I
wasn't so much and I emphasize this I need to know what values of T 1 depends
需要知道T 1的值取决于WT来防御W，所以这是
need to know what values of T 1 depends on WT to defense of W so this is the
on WT to defense of W so this is the graphical representation in a period
在称为它的时期中的图形表示变得微不足道，并使之变得微不足道
graphical representation in a period called it becomes trivial and to make it
called it becomes trivial and to make it interesting and this is the type of
有趣的是，这是我们上一次做的关系问题的类型
interesting and this is the type of relationship problem we did last it has
relationship problem we did last it has high parameters to me and we almost have
对我来说参数很高，我们几乎有参数alpha，如果您还
high parameters to me and we almost have the parameters alpha and if you also
the parameters alpha and if you also want to make this values of P n to be
想要使P n的值在某些未知噪声西格玛的情况下嘈杂
want to make this values of P n to be noisy with some unknown noise Sigma
noisy with some unknown noise Sigma square then this is the very general
平方，那么这是贝叶斯回归的非常笼统的描述
square then this is the very general description of a Bayesian regression
description of a Bayesian regression model okay I know there is a lot there
模型好吧，我知道那里很多，但您可能需要学习
model okay I know there is a lot there but you may need to study
but you may need to study all right but the equation is for every
好的，但是等式在每个方面都正确我测量了终点，
all right but the equation is for every extent all right I measured the end and
extent all right I measured the end and my actual you know function very
我实际的情况特别是从一开始就知道一些噪音
my actual you know function very especially from the end by some noise
especially from the end by some noise Sigma square that I got of what it is ok
我在回归模型中可以得到的西格玛平方，我需要这些
Sigma square that I got of what it is ok in my regression model I need these
in my regression model I need these coefficients w all right that define my
可以定义我的回归函数的系数
coefficients w all right that define my regression function and
regression function and the memory is the same regardless of n
内存是相同的，而不管n小n，并且因为我放置了先前的LW
the memory is the same regardless of n little n and because I put a prior LW
little n and because I put a prior LW that has some macabre parameter salsa I
有一些令人毛骨悚然的参数莎莎，我基本上需要从
that has some macabre parameter salsa I need to basically have an arrow from
need to basically have an arrow from alpha to W so this model represents the
相对于W的alpha，因此该模型表示的联合分布看起来像这样
alpha to W so this model represents the joint distribution that looks like this
joint distribution that looks like this okay
好的，这是难得的权利，所以这是
okay again there is rare right so this is the
again there is rare right so this is the joint distribution of things I observed
我观察到的事物的联合分布，这就是嘈杂的功能评估
joint distribution of things I observed which is this noisy function evaluations
which is this noisy function evaluations and the parameters given the inputs X
给定输入X的参数，现在输入就进入了这种状态
and the parameters given the inputs X now the inputs come here this kind of
now the inputs come here this kind of economic the social time given the no
鉴于没有我不知道的单一平方和联合，因此节省了社会时间
economic the social time given the no single square I don't know and the Joint
single square I don't know and the Joint Distribution you can read it from the
您可以从图表中读取分布，但对于从未见过的人
Distribution you can read it from the graph but for those who have never seen
graph but for those who have never seen this glass before and they know about
这杯酒，他们基本上了解回归，这就是力量
this glass before and they know about regression basically this is the power
regression basically this is the power the Joint Distribution is the player
联合发行人是玩家，这是您可以想到的写照
the Joint Distribution is the player this is you can think of this portray
this is you can think of this portray the Joint Distribution as the UH
UH对工作室进行归一化可以很好地进行联合发行，所以
the Joint Distribution as the UH normalize for studio all right okay so
normalize for studio all right okay so it is the prior the depends on Alpha
这是之前依赖Alpha的部分，例如那部分锁定，然后
it is the prior the depends on Alpha like that that part of it lock and then
like that that part of it lock and then you have the right we could model that
您有权利，我们可以进行建模，从而为您提供TN的概率
you have the right we could model that gives you the probability of TN give an
gives you the probability of TN give an extent but that probability depends of
范围，但该概率取决于噪声Sigma平方和函数
extent but that probability depends of the noise Sigma square and the function
the noise Sigma square and the function W so effectively we don't have to write
如此有效，如果我看着这个，我们不必写这个冗长的方程式
W so effectively we don't have to write this lengthy equation if I look at this
this lengthy equation if I look at this graph I know what is going on and I know
图，我知道发生了什么，我知道问题出在哪里，这就是为什么何时
graph I know what is going on and I know where the problem is and that's why when
where the problem is and that's why when you've got the homework problem Subic
你有家庭作业的问题苏比克说他们知道一切，所以让我给
you've got the homework problem Subic said they know everything so let me give
said they know everything so let me give the report then you figure out what it
报告，然后您弄清楚这意味着什么，这是一个方程式，这是一个
the report then you figure out what it means says here is an equation here's a
means says here is an equation here's a plot going away the problem to do this
情节消失解决这个问题好吗，所以基本上我们需要什么程序
plot going away the problem to do this okay so what program basically we need
okay so what program basically we need to require that you understand that this
要求您了解此图表示现在所有这些都可以
to require that you understand that this graph implies all of this ok now in
graph implies all of this ok now in is there is nothing for predictions
没有什么可以预测的，基本上只有信息
is there is nothing for predictions basically it has only the information
basically it has only the information the values for training the T values and
用于训练T值和X值的海啸之前的值，但是
the values for training the T values and the X values the prior tsunami but
the X values the prior tsunami but there's nothing of prediction so if you
没有任何预测，所以如果您想添加一些东西进行预测，那么
there's nothing of prediction so if you want to add things for prediction so
want to add things for prediction so don't let's say not going to train the
别说不去训练模型，今天也要训练新的X
don't let's say not going to train the model but also today both for a new X to
model but also today both for a new X to predict what the value of the function
预测功能的价值是心脏这是整个图
predict what the value of the function is the heart this is the whole diagram
is the heart this is the whole diagram that includes the joint probability
包括所有事物的联合概率分布，所以
that includes the joint probability distribution of everything so the
distribution of everything so the distribution of W the take data that you
W的分布，您给出的汇整数据以及您的预测T
distribution of W the take data that you gave but also the prediction T that you
gave but also the prediction T that you want to do at that point X and you
想要在X点做，您会发现它包含ANOVA谎言
want to do at that point X and you notice it contains the ANOVA lies
notice it contains the ANOVA lies posterior which is the prior times the
后验，这是先前的可能性再次出现的可能性
posterior which is the prior times the likelihood all right this comes again
likelihood all right this comes again from what we did before but also now it
从我们以前做过的事情到现在都有的事情，所以这是您所知道的
from what we did before but also now it has so this is sort of where you know
has so this is sort of where you know the posterior value you literally times
您的后验值实际上乘以可能性与可能性的乘积
the posterior value you literally times the likelihood okay and the likelihood
the likelihood okay and the likelihood from the prediction point is between UW
从预测的角度来看，在UW和她之间
from the prediction point is between UW and she was square for my